Previously on From...
Ever since you fell asleep
and your eyes got all white,
you've been different.
All I remember is being more scared
than I've ever been in my entire life.
You really need to get some rest.
Boyd said it was okay to sleep again.
It's not that. It's...
I feel like something is watching me.
Help me.
You're... you're Victor's father.
Miranda used to call it the bottle tree.
The original is in a park
a few towns over.
You need to take me there right now.
Where am I?
There's a tree in the
middle of the road.
Just take a detour!
- Go around it!
- You have to listen to me.
It's not safe to stop out
here once it gets dark.
There are things in this
town that will hurt us.
- Jim!
- Tabitha.
Please help us!
There's a toolkit on the bus. I got it.
I can't find the fucking keys!
Are you looking for these?
We get to keep Randall, though.
What the fuck?
- What was that?
- Nicky's been shot!
She's bleeding internally.
Nicky, stay with me.
You look much better.
You've been eating a little more?
Yeah.
Finally found something
I could keep down.
Donna?
Why is this happening?
Why can't they stop?
Everyone out of the way.
Out of the way!
- Clear a path!
- We're gonna need some fresh towels!
Okay. This needs moving.
Okay, okay. Out of the way.
Out of the way.
All right. Get him down.
Hurry!
- Please. Please!
- What happened?
Jesus.
Tell us what you need.
Easy.
Here.
I need something to clean
and stitch his face,
- and I need more towels!
- Why would they do this?
Boyd?
All right. Okay.
- Stop! Okay.
- No, no, no. It's all right.
Stop. Take it easy. Take it easy.
Take it easy.
No, no, no.
You're gonna hurt yourself. You're
gonna hurt yourself. Take it easy.
You did this. You fucking
left me out there, man.
You fucking left me out there!
You did this. You fucking left me!
www.subtitulamos.tv
What happened?
Where the hell did that come from?
- Okay. Easy.
- It was a long night. Come on.
- Is everyone okay?
- Yeah.
Kristi!
- Oh, my God!
- I'm okay.
- Jesus.
- Okay. It could have been a lot worse.
- Here. Let's get you inside.
- Yep. Careful.
- I got her.
- Okay.
Where's the food?
Dale and the others are
bringing it to storage.
What the hell happened last night?
Boyd.
Tabitha's back.
What?
She was on the ambulance
when it came into town.
How?
Those weird trees in the
forest, she went through one.
She said it took her to a lighthouse.
There's a meeting in the
diner this afternoon.
- Hey!
- It's okay.
Just let him go.
Let's go. All right.
Okay.
I don't think that's quite your style.
I was told I could look through these.
Of course. What's ours is yours.
Thanks.
I... I've sent some people
out to look for Victor.
It's not a big town.
If I'd known was gonna see him...
I would have worn a better shirt.
You know what?
There is a closet upstairs
where we keep the good stuff.
How 'bout we get you fixed up?
I'd appreciate that.
Okay. Let's do that.
Come on.
Up here.
I thought you said Jasper
was in the tunnels.
He is. We need supplies.
We can't go into the tunnels
unless we have supplies.
What supplies?
We need to make sure we don't get lost.
What happened?
Last night was...
It was a bad night.
I'll wait outside.
Victor.
Who died?
Nicky.
And Randall got pretty torn up.
He's at the clinic now.
I need some things from my room.
Look, Victor.
Here. Come. Come. With me.
Come on.
Something else happened last night.
What?
- Tabitha came back.
- Really?
And she had someone with her.
Victor, your dad is here.
- That's not possible. He...
- He's upstairs.
- No.
- Look, look.
- I know this is a lot to take in.
- No.
- No. No.
- Victor.
No.
- Victor?
- No!
That was quick. Did you...
Victor! Where are you going?
Victor, will you please
just tell me what happened?
I thought you said we
were going to get Jasper.
Hey, stop!
You're not being fair.
You came into my house,
you made me sit in that fort, and now...
Donna said my dad is here.
What? How?
It doesn't matter. You should go home.
We'll get Jasper later.
So, what was it like?
It was...
You know, it was scary,
waking up in the hospital,
not knowing if it was...
real or if I was still dreaming.
So, you really talked to Grandma?
I did.
I just don't understand.
How do you go from a
lighthouse in the woods
to a hospital in Maine?
Honey, I don't know.
I wish I could explain.
The important thing is that she's back,
and we're all together.
Hey!
I need to talk to you.
- Back off, man.
- No, no, no. No.
Jim, it's okay. It's okay.
Please.
Boyd said...
Boyd said you went through a tree?
They're called Farway trees.
There's a bunch of them in the forest,
but this one has bottles on it.
The lighthouse.
Was it the same lighthouse
Miranda was looking for?
I mean, it has to be.
Can you get back there without the tree?
I don't know. I don't know.
Okay. Then we need to go to the tree.
All right. So, hold on.
She just got back, and
you want to do what?
I'm not saying go through it
again, but I need to see it.
I've been there, okay?
It was the first place I looked
when she didn't come back.
There is nothing to see.
You mean besides the magic tree.
Okay. The bottles. What
about the bottles?
- Was there anything special about them?
- I took a few of 'em down.
There were slips of paper inside
with numbers written on them.
Oh, my God. And you don't
think that's important?
I think this place does
a pretty great job
on messing with our heads.
Wait. No. This is different.
It has to be.
Look. I get that this place
is one giant mindfuck, but...
Pardon my French.
But she went home, okay?
That's not a trick. It's not a dream!
That's real, and there is a
whole town full of people
who are gonna be banging down
your door demanding answers
whether you have them or not.
Take me to the tree.
Let's see if we can find some.
I told Boyd that I was gonna
go to that town meeting.
Oh, fuck the town meeting! Sorry. Sorry.
Okay. Look.
Town meeting isn't gonna solve anything,
but going to the tree,
at least it's a start.
We had to leave some of the
food back at the settlement.
We...
we'll probably need to send another team
out before the next snowfall.
Yeah. We'll figure it out.
Boyd, there is something out there,
something different.
We heard it both times now,
walking around outside
the cabins at night.
Okay.
If walking around is all it's doing,
then, we got bigger
things to worry about.
What they did to Randall...
Why'd they leave him alive?
Why not just kill him?
I think they want us to look at him.
When the sun's up,
they want us to remember
what's coming at night.
Part of the thing that
keeps people sane here
is we get to pretend during the daytime,
pretend that we're safe.
With Randall walking around,
then we don't get to pretend anymore.
I removed the bullet, stabilized her.
One minute, she was fine, and
then all of a sudden, she wasn't.
Jesus.
- Sorry.
- Yeah.
Okay.
God. It's a miracle
there are no fractures.
- Mari.
- Probably have ligament damage.
This should be elevated. I'm
gonna get you another pillow.
Mari, just stop for a second, please.
Look, last night wasn't easy,
and it wasn't your fault, okay?
Yeah, well...
- tell that to Nicky.
- I'm telling you.
Look. I know what it's like. I just...
I don't... I don't want you to...
What?
If you think I'm gonna start spiraling
- and stealing morphine again...
- I didn't say that.
You didn't have to.
Hey. Come here.
Come here.
Hey, you are the patient right now.
Can you please just
stop worrying about me
and let me worry about you?
Can we worry about each other?
I gotta go.
- Wait.
- Just get some rest, yeah?
- No. Boyd...
- I just wanna help.
I understand that.
Boyd, you being here is just
gonna make things worse.
I'm sorry.
No.
You're right.
Look, people need you out there.
They're gonna need you
at the meeting later.
Both of you.
There's only so much people can take,
and now, with Tabitha being back,
the fact that she went home...
- I gotta...
- Yeah.
Hey, Randall. It's okay.
Squeeze my hand.
- I'm going to take a look.
- All right.
- Yeah.
You're okay.
This is where he stays...
most of the time.
It's...
It's a little different
from his room at home.
For the first few years,
every time I'd turn a corner,
there'd be this little spark of hope
that maybe, just maybe,
I'd see all of them there...
Miranda, Eloise, Victor.
And they'd smile and laugh.
We'd all cry together about what
a terrible mistake it all was.
Then...
That was the hardest part...
that little bit of hope.
That was the part I couldn't bear.
As the years went by,
it became easier to tell myself
they were dead.
They were gone.
So, that's what I did.
All that time, my little boy was here,
alone.
What kind of man gives up on his family?
No wonder he doesn't wanna talk to me.
Just give him a little time.
He'll come 'round.
Sorry to interrupt,
but we're all heading to the meeting.
I'll be right there.
Meeting?
People have a lot of questions
about what happened,
about Tabitha.
Sure.
It was kind of a big deal
that she got out of here.
Come on.
Come on!
Okay, everybody, just take a seat.
- Hey, come on in.
- Sit down here.
Everybody grab a seat.
All right, everybody. Okay. All right.
All right. Look.
I understand that everybody
wants answers, right?
So do I, all right?
But the truth is,
there's no easy explanations
to any of this, okay?
- There's nothing that...
- Where the hell is Tabitha?
- Yeah.
She's coming, all right?
Just try to remember,
she's been through a lot.
All due respect, Boyd, but
we've all been through a lot.
That's right.
- I understand that.
- Are you sure?
'Cause I feel like if you had
any clue about anything,
she'd be the one talking instead of you.
Yeah.
Look. Everybody calm the fuck down.
Hey, why were you in the ambulance?
Well, we were in an accident.
I was taking Tabitha
to a park near my...
Tabitha's here.
What do I say?
Just tell 'em the truth.
- Thanks for coming.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
Did you really go through a tree?
- Hey, let's let her talk.
- It's okay.
I did. Yes.
I imagine some of you
already know this,
but, there are some trees in the forest
that aren't like the other trees.
Hey. Town meeting's already started.
Yeah. I just gotta grab something.
Hello?
Why did you bring me here?
'Cause I wanted you to see
that if you climb high enough,
even a nightmare can look like a dream.
Hello?
Hey, Elgin.
Oh, my...
- What the fuck?
- I'm so sorry.
- I thought you...
- Oh, my God.
- I'm sorry.
- Are you okay?
No.
Not really.
- I'm sorry.
- No. Wait.
I could use some company,
if you're not, you know, busy.
Sure.
Victor?
What are you doing? It's cold out here.
I never drew pictures of him.
What?
When I was alone here, I never...
I always drew pictures
of things that I saw,
because I knew the pictures
would remember, but I never...
I never drew...
pictures of what came before.
And now I told myself that
was a dream and that...
that...
he was...
Victor...
None of that matters.
He's here.
Somehow, your father is here,
and he's waiting for you back in town.
No. No. He's waiting for a little boy
that drove away a long time ago.
What's he gonna think...
when he sees... me?
I don't know.
I know I'm supposed to tell you that
it'll be okay,
and he'll love you no matter what.
But I don't know if that's true.
You're really bad at this.
Sorry.
I don't know you that well,
but you seem like a really good person,
and that's something
to be proud of here.
I would give anything
to feel like a good person again.
Maybe...
Maybe you're not the
only one who's afraid.
Maybe he's afraid of not being the dad
that little boy remembers.
So, you see this woman in the
kimono even when you're awake?
Now, I do. Yeah.
Is she trying to hurt you?
I thought she was at first,
but when I saw her last night,
she asked me for my help.
With what?
I don't know.
If my grandma was here, she'd probably
tell me it was an angel or somethin'.
"Remember now, there's a reason
why angels say 'Fear not'
when they saw someone.
Even Gabriel was terrifying."
Look at you, Mr. Bible Study.
You wanna know the fucked up part?
I would take the creepy
kimono woman in a heartbeat
over the shit I hear in my head now.
Like what?
Mostly just screaming.
But I don't...
I don't just hear it. It's like...
It's like I can feel it, too.
This is the only thing
that makes it quiet.
You talk to your folks about it?
What are they gonna do?
They're in the diner right
now with everyone else,
trying to figure out what it
means that my mom got out.
What do you think it means?
Honestly, I don't think
it means anything.
I think this whole place exists...
I think it's just here
to make us suffer.
Maybe that's why it let her out.
What do you mean?
Best way to make us suffer
is to give us hope.
I don't think it's ever gonna let us go.
You're so depressing when you're stoned.
Sorry.
And then the next thing I knew,
the ambulance had stopped.
The driver said that there was a
tree in the middle of the road,
and you all know how
things go from there.
Come on in.
When you were out there
did you contact anyone?
Did you let the police,
anyone know about this place?
I really wanted to.
Are you fucking kidding me?
- Watch your mouth.
- Come on.
That could be it.
You don't understand. They
wouldn't have believed me.
Tabitha, you don't know that.
Look. All due respect, when she told me,
I thought she was out of her mind.
But you believed her.
Eventually, you believed her.
To be fair, my circumstances
are a little different
than the average person.
Look. I was in the ambulance
when she was begging us to turn around,
and we thought she was hysterical.
What is she even doing here?
- She killed someone last night.
- Yeah.
- All right. Oh, hey, hey!
- Come on!
- Look. That was an accident.
- Accident?
Yeah, sure. Everything's an accident
unless it's somebody that you
and Queen Bee here don't like.
I'm sorry to say this, but
you had an opportunity
that none of us have ever had before,
and you blew it.
- Excuse me.
- We're just waiting here.
What exactly would you have done?
What would any of you have done?
I wouldn't have taken a
day trip to the park.
- Yeah. Something.
- That's not what it was.
- I wasn't taking a day trip.
- You were out there
in the real world where people can help.
How could you not take
advantage of that?
Yeah, they may have
thought you were crazy,
but what if they didn't?
What if somebody believed you?
Someone believed me,
and look where he is!
He's sitting right here with us!
- Tabitha.
- Look. I'm sure everyone
could have done a better
job than what I did,
and I'm so sorry you didn't
have that opportunity.
I'm sorry I don't have your answers.
I'm sorry. I can't do this.
I can't do this. I'm sorry.
- Please.
- Tabitha.
Not now. That's enough.
Oh, my God.
Listen.
Listen. The most important
part of all of this,
the thing that we cannot lose sight of
is Tabitha got out.
For all the good it seems to have done.
No, no, but it's not about the
fact that she is back here.
It's that someone got home.
It's not just hoping
and wishing anymore.
We have concrete proof now.
It's possible.
Great. Where's the tree?
What?
Where... is... the... tree?
- Yeah!
- Yeah.
Everybody just calm down.
Slow down for a second.
- We gotta think about this, okay?
- What is there to think about?
Tabitha went through the
tree and got home, right?
Why aren't we all lining
up to do the same?
Because it's not that simple, okay?
We can't just run out
there into the forest
and hop into the first tree that we see!
Why not?
Excuse me?
I just... I'm sorry, Boyd.
I don't wanna be here a second
longer than I have to be.
Even if there is the slightest chance
that this tree can get us home,
what are we waiting for?
- Okay. Everybody just...
- No, no, no.
Dad, Dad, she's right, okay?
- We can't just sit here and talk all day...
- Okay! Stop, stop, stop, stop!
No! Listen! Hey, hey, hey!
You're all assuming that this tree is
some kind of magic door. It's not.
I went through one of those trees,
and you know where I ended up?
In a chimney underground.
Damn near killed myself.
- Look.
- You don't...
It wasn't even the tree
that got her out of here.
She said it was the lighthouse.
Great. Let's just get to the lighthouse,
- and then we'll go home.
- Listen to me, okay?
No, you fucking listen!
- Dale, come on!
- No, no, no! I've had it!
I've had it! Had it with your... plans.
I've had it with your fucking rules!
I wanna go home!
Why didn't you go to the meeting?
One thing you'll learn
when you're older,
any meeting with more than three
people is basically pointless.
- Jade?
- That was quick.
How'd it go?
Not great.
See?
We're going to the tree.
- Finally.
- Wait. What?
I have nothing to tell them, Jim.
They're right.
I went out. I went out, and I came back.
And I came back with nothing.
I owe it to them.
- You owe?
- Yes.
Tabitha, you just got back, and
now you wanna go back out there?
- It's not like she's gonna go
in the tree. - Exactly.
- Would you just stay outta this?
- I wanna go, too.
- No! Nobody is going to a tree.
- Jim!
- I need to speak with you
for a minute, please. - Yeah.
You need to think about
what you're doing.
I am.
We thought you were dead.
Your children thought you were dead.
You think I give a shit
about what you owe
to these people in a diner?
You owe it to your kids to be here now.
I'm just gonna show him
where the tree is.
That's all.
I'm not gonna go in.
I'll be back. I promise.
Fine, but Ethan...
he stays here with me.
Do you know he ran off looking
for you when you were gone?
Do you really wanna take him out there
and show him where the...
the magic tree is?
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Ethan,
you're gonna stay here
with your father, okay?
- But I wanna help.
- You're helping by staying here.
I'll be back soon.
- Let's go.
- I'll get my coat.
Dad.
Stop, Dad!
Come on.
- What the fuck is wrong with you?
- What?
We are sitting on a powder keg in there,
and you and Fatima are lighting matches.
- She's upset.
- Oh, yeah?
Well, guess what? We're
all fucking upset.
What we need to do is calm people down.
Okay, or maybe what we need is for someone
around here to start doing something
instead of sitting around worrying
about what could go wrong.
Is that what I'm doing? I'm just
sitting around. Is that it?
Maybe what we need is to
start taking chances.
Oh, you wanna take some chances. Okay.
Who you wanna take a chance on?
Whose life are you willing to
take a chance to gamble on?
- You know that's not what I'm saying.
- No, no! Tell me,
'cause I wanna know!
Who we gonna march out there next?
You wanna do something, right?
So tell me! Who's next?
Who's your pick?
Exactly.
What happened in there...
is a dangerous thing.
It's a dangerous...
I never realized all this
stuff was down here.
Yeah. This is where they store
the surplus of weird.
I couldn't sleep one night,
and, I found this.
Oh, my God.
This is, like...
It's, like, the vintage motherlode.
Oh, no. No. It's not just vintage.
This shit is...
This is '80s vintage.
Can you imagine people
running through the woods
in, like, fluorescent spandex?
With their big-ass hair getting
caught in the branches?
Hold on.
Oh, no way.
Wait. Wait.
Like, come on.
Yeah. Hey, that's it.
That's it right there.
Yeah, right?
Hey, check this out.
Yeah. We're very post-apocalyptic chic.
No. Don't do that.
Oh, shit.
Think it still works?
Oh, no. This is mine.
- What?
- Like...
All right.
I'm keeping that.
No. You got one for yourself.
Elgin.
Come on. Please?
- You have to come get it, then.
- That's not fair.
Sheriff Boyd?
You got a second?
I wanted to thank you for
what you said in there.
I can't take back what I did.
I know that, but I think I can help.
Oh, yeah?
How's that?
The meeting today...
Look, if you want them to
stop focusing on that tree,
you have to give them
something else to focus on,
a project or...
We had this really big storm.
It hit the coast last year,
and it flooded half the town,
knocked out all the power.
And people were scared. They were angry.
And so the precinct captain,
he got everyone out to
sandbag the marina.
The worst of the storm had already
passed, but it gave people...
it gave them something to focus on.
It made them feel like they
had some sort of control.
I see.
So, you've been here less than a day,
and already, you've got the solution.
That's not what I'm saying.
- I'm just...
- You think I stuck up for you in there?
You think we're buddies now?
The one thing I agreed to
was that you didn't belong
in that goddamn room.
- What happened last night...
- You killed someone!
And you left two people
to die in that ambulance.
- I know!
- One of whom
you handcuffed to a fucking wall!
- I am sorry.
- Great!
Go be sorry, then. Try
not to kill anybody.
You let me worry about how to
take care of my goddamn town.
Thank you!
Fuck.
God.
Baby, what are you... What's going on?
- Hey, how did it go with your dad?
- It was fine. What are you doing?
I was just, checking the supplies,
- the crops and...
- Hey, hold on. Hold on.
- What? What do you want? What?
- Okay. Look.
I'm trying to be supportive.
- Okay, so...
- And I'm trying...
I'm trying to be patient, but I...
- I need...
- You can't help.
- What do you...
- You can't fucking help!
Look, babe. I don't understand.
- Look! You...
- What do you mean I can't help?
You can't fucking help! This.
- This is all I can keep down.
- What?
I think there's something wrong...
with the baby. I think there's
something wrong with the baby.
Something's not right with the baby.
What are you looking at?
Well, there's a motel sign here.
There's a pool.
Where's the motel?
Are you Victor's dad?
That's right.
You must be Ethan.
Your mom told me all about you.
Thanks for bringing her back.
I didn't...
You're welcome.
I'm going to the barn
to feed the animals.
Wanna come?
Sure.
Have you seen Victor yet?
No.
I don't think he's very
happy that I'm here.
Why?
For one thing,
he found out I was here,
and he just ran off.
He does stuff like that sometimes.
He gets really grumpy.
I don't think he means to.
You know him pretty well, uh?
He's my best friend.
Sometimes, he gets so grumpy,
he says we can't be friends anymore.
But I think that's just
'cause he's scared.
What do you think he's scared of?
That I'm gonna die.
Everyone he ever loved here died.
I can come with you,
if you want,
up to Colony House. You don't have to...
What's wrong?
Oh, there's Victor.
It's okay.
Everything's okay.
Victor?
Victor.
Hey, hey, hey.
No, no.
Oh, God.
I didn't know how to get home.
It's okay.
What are you doing in here?
Just...
I don't know.
Trying to assuage my guilt, I guess.
What happened last night
wasn't your fault,
and I'm sorry I wasn't more
supportive at the meeting.
People have a right to ask questions.
I'm just tired of being the
guy without any answers.
Something about that funny to you?
Sorry. It's just,
you sound like my sister.
She was always...
She was someone
who tried so hard to
make everything right,
and she always ended up
feeling like she was wrong.
The way everyone's acting in there,
it's like they wanna
go home and you don't.
You're trying to keep people
from doing something stupid.
I just want you to know that
I'll have your back next time.
Yeah. Thank you.
Come on.
Oh, goddamn it!
Hey, I don't suppose you
wanna climb up here
- and maybe help me...
- They're just numbers.
No, no, no. But look. Look.
Every single slip of paper has
four numbers on it, right?
What if they're not just numbers?
What if they're dates?
This one says 2659.
I don't know, Jade. Maybe Jim's right.
How do we know that everything that...
I...
I saw your freaky kids, you know.
Really?
Where?
Down in the tunnels.
I went down there the day you...
I was hoping to find
something to help Julie.
Instead, I saw this.
Turns out it wasn't a symbol.
It was a hole in the ceiling,
and these slashes
were roots.
And those kids...
they were laid out on slabs of stone,
repeating that word over and over again.
Anghkooey.
When I tell you I felt
fear in that moment
like I've never felt in my life...
But there was also this...
this glimpse of something that I
knew was there but I couldn't...
Even with all the fucking
horror, it was like,
for the first time,
I felt like there were threads
that were finally starting to connect.
Connect how?
I don't know.
Piecing this together, it's like, it's,
it's like trying to grab hold of water.
These numbers in these bottles,
they might seem like this tree.
There is no denying what this tree did,
and the fact that someone took the time
to put these bottles here,
to put these numbers here...
It only looks like chaos
until you understand the pattern.
So, this is the mysterious tree, uh?
Fuck me.
Bottles are a nice touch.
What are you doing here?
This is it?
I just... just go in here?
I really... I wouldn't
do that if I were you.
Well...
you're not me.
And that's why you're
gonna be sitting here
with your thumb up your
ass while I'm back home
figuring out how to get help
for everybody back here.
See, that's what a
smart person would do.
Dale.
Dale! Dale.
Dale. Dale.
Look.
Somebody's gotta try, right?
It's okay. You guys can thank me later.
Look, Boyd. If you need anything,
just, you know, just...
He's over here!
Yeah! Someone's over here!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
All right, everybody.
Everyone just back up.
Move back. Back up.
Oh, Jesus.
Okay.
Can you help him?
Okay. Okay.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Let me...
Let me...
I'm sorry, Dale.
I'm so sorry this happened to you.
Oh, fuck.
Okay.
All right. Who's...
who's next?
Still wanna go through the tree?
Go ahead, then!
Who the fuck is next?!
You think I wanna do this?!
You think I wanna be the one who...
I am trying to keep you alive!
Don't you see that?!
I can't help you if you don't let me!
I can't...
Hey...
www.subtitulamos.tv