Previously on From...
I'm sorry. This is the only way.
- Where am I?
- You're in Camden, Maine.
Get the hell outta here. You deaf?
I said get the...
Where did you get that?
You're Victor's father.
I'm gonna go look for my wife.
Someone's gotta make sure that
Jim comes back in one piece.
I know what it's like
to lose a parent here,
and I'm not gonna watch
Julie and Ethan lose
both their parents in the same week.
- _
- Ma...
_
What the fuck?
These look pretty solid.
We could just start from
here in the morning.
- Just give me a second.
- Come on!
My stomach just hasn't been right.
Those animals are the only
food that we have now.
They are a resource. We have
to make everything lasts!
There's goddamn cows in the street!
Get those smaller animals into the barn!
- Alma's outside!
- No! Go! Ethan, run!
Julie! Go!
Let's go! Come on!
- No, no, no! You go back!
- We do together!
- No!
- Boyd!
- You think this place can't break you?
Let's see.
What the fuck?!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
I know, I know, I know!
I know! I know! I know!
Don't.
Somebody has to go and see.
Oh, God. No, Jesus, no.
Boyd.
Boyd!
Key.
Boyd.
Where's the key?
In my pocket.
They left it in my pocket.
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry!
Please...
Kenny!
No. No.
You gotta come down here!
Look at this.
It's growing in patches
all around the lake.
There's enough food here to feed
everybody in the entire town.
Look.
www.subtitulamos.tv
What happened?
Oh, no. It's okay.
You...
You passed out on my front porch.
Maybe I should just...
You should sit.
Okay. Okay. I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- You showed up on my doorstep
with the lunchbox my son
left here with...
a very long time ago.
You're gonna tell me how you found that,
and you're gonna tell me right now.
Okay.
Yeah.
My name is Tabitha Matthews.
My family and I were on a road trip
to see some relatives in Colorado,
when we had to take a
detour off the highway.
There was a massive tree
in the middle of the road,
so we thought we were
just driving around it.
But we never got back to the road.
We kept driving, and we
got to this... town,
a place that we couldn't leave.
But there were people there,
and some of them had
been there for a while.
- I don't know how long they'd been...
- No, no!
Where did you get the lunchbox?
Well, that's what I'm
trying to tell you.
The place we ended up,
there are people that had been
there for years, I mean, for...
Where did you get the lunchbox?!
- He gave it to me!
- Who?
Your son. Victor. He gave it to me.
He gave it to you.
Yeah.
When?
Three, four... Four days ago.
Victor is alive.
The town I was telling you about, he's
been stuck there all these years.
Okay, all right.
If you won't talk to me, then
maybe you'll talk to the police.
No, sir. Please, please.
You can't call them.
I can't tell them who I am.
If I try to explain any of this
to them, I'll sound crazy.
When they ask where my family is...
what am I gonna tell them?
I don't know where they are.
Please, sir, you have to believe me.
Please don't call the police.
Well, Tabitha, I called the
police about 20 minutes ago.
They should be here any minute.
So, we're just gonna
sit here together...
until they arrive.
I know how to prove I'm not lying.
No.
You don't come in here. You understand?
Boyd might be okay with
everything you did,
- but if you think for a second...
- Tian-Chen died.
What?
Something happened last night.
The animals...
got out into the street,
and she...
I didn't...
I thought you would want to know,
and I wasn't sure if anyone...
I'm sorry.
Kristi?
Who was that?
Baby?
Hey, what's wrong?
What?
Kenny's mom died.
Over there.
Okay.
Here. Okay.
We...
We need to...
We need to make sure she gets
buried with her husband.
She would have wanted that.
She wouldn't...
Right.
Yeah.
- Boyd.
- Yeah.
You were in the barn with
her, with those things.
Yeah.
How are you still alive?
They wanted me to watch.
They...
Yeah.
No! Let me go!
Boyd!
Is it true?
Oh, fuck.
I wanna go see her.
I just I don't think that
a good idea right now, okay?
She's gonna be okay, right?
Kristi can fix her.
Ethan...
We should bring her her blanket.
She'll be more comfortable
when she has her blanket.
- I wanna go see her.
- It's okay.
Tell her that we have
to go see Tian-Chen!
That we have to help!
- I could use a little help in there.
- No.
I have to go.
- You have to go?
- Yes, I have to go.
- I'm talking to you!
- I have to go!
Wait! Where are you going?
- I can't stay here anymore.
- Why?
- Because!
- We have to help her!
We can't help her! She's dead!
She's dead, Ethan!
People die here!
I told you that! It's not make-believe!
I told you that bad things happen here!
It's not my fault that
you didn't listen!
I have to go.
It's okay.
_
I mean, there's other
people you can look up.
Boyd Stevens. His family went missing.
Donna.
Donna...
Okay.
Liu! Liu! Tian-Chen and Kenny Liu.
That family... that family's there, too.
You're lying.
I don't know how you're doing this,
- but you're lying.
- No, no. No, no, no, no, no.
I swear to you I'm not.
I swear on my children's lives.
My family is trapped, and
Victor is trapped, too.
Then how did you get here?
You want me to believe you just
happen to be the one person
who somehow managed to escape
this terrifying place?
Listen, I don't
understand, but yes, yes.
- And Victor helped me.
- No, don't...
Please.
Victor is a good man.
He's nice and sweet,
and my son loves him.
And my daughter... He
saved my daughter's life.
I thought that if I saved the
children locked in the tower, then...
somehow, I could save her from
whatever's happening to her...
What did you say?
Well, when I was in town, I
started seeing children,
or at least imagining I was.
And they were really frightening.
Victor said that they were
children locked in the tower,
that if I saved them,
then maybe I could...
I could somehow help my daughter
from what she's going through,
and I don't know if I'm doing it...
- Camden PD!
- Please.
Don't let them in. Please.
Please.
I'm not lying. I'm not lying.
Henry! Henry, you in there?
Hey, man.
I screwed up, man. I
thought I had an intruder
and turned out to be just
a dog off the leash.
The owner came back to...
Look, I owe you a dozen, okay?
I'm sorry.
All right, Henry. Take care of yourself.
Yeah, you, too. Yeah, I'm sorry. Thanks.
I, bought that almost 40 years ago...
a few years after my family disappeared.
I never once had the courage
to even load it, much less...
I'm gonna make you something to eat.
It was an ambush.
They knew we'd go after the animals.
Goddamn things opened the pen
and just waited for us
to walk right to them.
How many did you save?
What's... What?
Animals.
How many did you save?
Was it worth it?
Risking everyone's lives, for what?
An extra goat? A cow?
How much better off are we
today than we were yesterday?
Wait, wait.
Are you saying that I had a choice?
- Those animals are all we have!
- No, Boyd!
We are all we have!
Us! These people! This family!
That is all we've got, and
now we've got one less!
So, what was I supposed to do?!
Just stand there, watching
our only resource
go wandering off into the woods?
- We would have starved!
- We would have found another way!
Yesterday you were ready to
crawl into a fucking hole
because the crops had spoiled!
And now you're standing
there, telling me
that we would have found another way?!
That I shoulda just... I shoulda...
That I should just... get
the fuck outta here!
- What the fuck am I...
- No, okay, No, you're right.
You're right. You did
what you had to do.
You did the only thing you could do.
And you lost...
because the game here
is fucking rigged.
And no matter what hand
you play, you lose.
- Donna. Donna.
- No, no, no.
I'm not angry at you, Boyd. I'm not.
I'm angry at me.
Angry at me
because you told us that,
someday, we'd go home...
and I was stupid enough to believe it.
- I'm...
- Get off!
We gotta dress that cow
before the meat spoils.
Hey. You been in there for a while.
You okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- You know, I was thinking,
maybe we should go see Kristi,
just as a precaution.
Look, that's not necessary.
It's just morning sickness.
Can you at least open the door?
Give me a second!
You know, why don't I go see if Kristi
can just come up here, and
that way, you can just stay?
Look, I said I'm fine!
I don't need everybody...
It doesn't feel right.
You're not sleeping.
You're barely eating.
Fatima?
Fatima? Hey, look, come on.
What's going on?
Fatima, you're scaring me. Come on.
Can you please open the door?
I think you're right. Maybe
we should go see Kristi.
Kristi?
You here?
Wait here.
- Hello!
- Coming!
- Hey.
- Is Kristi here?
She's... She's down in town.
She's taking the news about
Tian-Chen pretty hard.
Listen, this can totally wait.
- The poor woman...
- No, it really can't.
Come on in. I'll take a look at you.
You know what? Maybe we
should wait for Kristi.
Kristi's dealing with a lot right now.
Yeah, but...
Look, no offense. You're not a doctor.
I am, however, a pediatric nurse.
So, as far as pregnancy goes,
I've pretty much seen everything.
Come on. Come.
Kinda cold out for a swim.
What are you doing out here?
I just realized that...
I can't even remember
whose truck this was.
That's how many people we...
Danny.
And his... his girlfriend Shay.
Right.
Danny and Shay.
They were good kids, yeah.
What happened last night...
it wasn't your fault.
You know, with all due respect, Kristi,
I'm not here for pep talks.
All due respect, Boyd, I
don't really give a shit.
Look, after what happened with Sara,
when she tried to hurt Ethan...
you sat with me in that diner
and you told me it wasn't my fault,
that it was this place,
that I had saved a lot of lives,
and that I was gonna save a hell of a lot
more by the time this all was finished.
So, was that just a bunch of
bullshit to make me feel better,
or did you mean it?
This isn't your fault. Okay?
Now, come on. Let's go
get you cleaned up.
Guys!
We found food!
Look! Look at this!
There's a... there's a lake,
and it's got everything.
It's got vegetables...
They found food!
All right.
There's, there's potatoes.
There might even be fish in the water.
What's going on?
Where are my kids?
They're fine.
They're okay.
Whose blood is that?
Kenny...
Where's...
Wait. Where's...
Where's my mom?
Kenny, maybe we should go inside.
Kenny.
Mom?
Ma!
Mom!
- Hey, Kenny...
- Stop! No, no, no, no, no.
- Hey, bud. Ken.
- No, stop!
- Bud, I'm...
- No.
- so s...
- Stop, stop.
- Listen, I'm so...
- No! No, no! Stop! Just...
- Stop.
- Okay.
Okay?
Okay. Yeah.
- I got it.
- Okay.
I'm so sorry. I'm so...
I'm so sorry.
Kenny, hey.
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
I'm okay.
I'm okay. I'm okay.
Where is she?
In the church.
I just...
I just... I need to sit
here for a minute.
- 'Kay?
- Yeah. Okay.
When was the last time you ate?
Three... four days?
She can't keep anything down.
I've tried to. It's just even
the smell of food, it's just...
Deep breath.
- Look, are you sure we shouldn't
just get Kristi? - Ellis, just...
How've you been doing since, you know...
Since what?
Since I went through withdrawal,
or since this place... mind-raped me?
Look, I know this is scary,
and if it's any consolation,
you're doing exactly what
you're supposed to be doing.
In the tradition of first-time
fathers everywhere,
you're scared out of your mind,
and you're asking every
question you possibly can.
As for you, you're
severely malnourished.
It's a wonder only one tooth fell out.
You also may have something
called hyperemesis gravidarum.
What is that? Is that bad?
It's essentially really
bad morning sickness.
We really just need to
get you eating again.
Okay.
You tell that to the
world's pickiest eater.
I'm gonna see if maybe we have something
that can settle your stomach.
But as far as the baby?
- Everything's okay?
- As far as I can tell,
everything's fine.
I'll be right back.
You see? I told you.
- Everything is okay.
- Was that you?
- Yeah.
- That was you?
Yeah, yeah, it was totally me, you know,
calm, cool, collected.
Yeah. Might have missed that.
You hear that in there?
Everything's gonna be okay.
Whenever things got
really bad here, she'd...
she used to always say...
"No matter how bad it gets,
we'll never have this day again."
She'd always repeat it
to make sure I got the message.
Did she...
Did she suffer?
- Kenny, I...
- No, I...
It's okay. You don't have to...
Have you seen her?
Have you seen what they did to her?
Not yet, no.
Whenever I think about my dad...
I can't...
All I can see is him lying
there in that basement.
I can't think of him and
not see him like that.
I don't want it to be like that for her.
Can you do me a favor?
Yeah, of course.
Can you...
Can you make her...
Can you make her look like her?
Can you make sure she looks nice?
She would be really upset, if she...
if she didn't look like her.
Yeah. Yeah, of course.
Thank you.
You... You need anything at all,
anything, you get someone
to come get me, okay?
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah.
? Celebrate good times! Come on! ?
? Let's celebrate ?
- ? Celebrate good times ?
- Stop it.
- ? come on! ?
- Stop.
? Let's celebrate ?
? There's a party going on right here ?
? A celebration to last... ?
- Stop!
- ? Throughout the year ?
Fucking stop! Shut the fuck up!
Stop! Fucking stop!
? We gonna celebrate
your party with you ?
? Come on now. Celebra... ?
You're back.
Yeah.
Tian-Chen is dead.
I know.
Ethan's upstairs.
- Julie...
- No.
Don't. Just please don't.
Julie, whatever you're
feeling right now,
it's okay.
No, it's not.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Ethan almost died, too.
Did you know that?
You should have been here, Dad. I...
I can't. I can't be like before.
Hey, hold on. What are
you talking about?
I can't be the fill-in parent
while you lose your shit.
I was looking for your mother.
Mom is gone! Okay? She's gone!
She went through a tree,
and now she's gone!
Don't know that.
Dad...
people can't survive more than a few
hours at night without a talisman.
She's been gone four days.
I know you feel bad that you
didn't stop her, but I can't...
When Thomas died, you
and Mom fell apart,
and there was no one there for Ethan.
I was 15.
I can't do it again.
I can't. Not this time.
I need you to get your
shit together. Okay?
Okay.
I don't get a lot of visitors.
At least now I know you
won't pass out on me.
Back before she disappeared,
my wife, Miranda,
started hearing voices.
She said they were children,
calling out to her,
that they were...
locked in a tower somewhere,
you know, crying out to be saved.
She was terrified of them.
The only person I ever repeated that to
was the investigating detective,
and he died 20 years ago.
When you're done, I-I
wanna show you something.
Yeah.
I want you to look at this room.
This is where my children slept.
My little boy.
My little girl.
They were the lights of my life.
And when they disappeared...
it ripped my life to pieces.
I didn't care about the accusations.
I didn't care that everyone
thought that I did it.
All I could think, all I could...
remember,
even now,
is that the last words I said to them,
"Clean your room or no TV."
And then, I went to work.
When I came home...
they were gone.
Why are you showing me this?
I don't know how you know
about those children my wife heard.
I don't know how you got a hold
of my son's lunchbox or...
or how you could have possibly
faked those articles online.
The only possible explanation
I can come up with...
is that you're actually...
telling the truth,
and that means my son is alive.
And that...
That means something I-I don't...
I don't even have the words to...
express.
So, if you...
if this isn't real...
you tell me right now.
If this is all just some
cruel, elaborate...
No, no, no, no, no. I
swear to you, it's not.
I believe that the reason
I was sent here...
was to find you.
No.
I think you're here for
what's in the basement.
I didn't want her to be alone.
She made me tea.
I'll give you some time.
Wait.
I have to...
fix her before Kenny sees her,
and I don't know how to do that.
I'm...
I'm not a mortician.
- I don't...
- Hey. Let me help you.
I used to play dress-up a lot as a kid.
We can do this. Right?
There we go.
All right, let's get you inside...
get you fed.
See if Marielle's magic
elixir does the trick, okay?
Why don't you go see your dad?
All I gotta do is get in bed,
and he's having a really hard day.
Are you sure?
Yeah. Go. Go. I love you.
I love you, too.
Here.
I'll be back soon.
- Give him my best, okay?
- Okay.
None of these are any good.
They're all gross.
Take those to the kitchen?
Are those the crops?
Yeah. We figured we'd
try composting them,
see if we can't get the
soil turned around.
- You think that'll work?
- Who the hell knows?
Sorry about yesterday,
the bathroom, I just...
It's okay. Everyone's on,
on edge these days, so...
Still, no reason to be a dick. Sorry.
Victor?
Ethan, what are you doing up here?
- Have you seen Victor?
- I haven't, no.
He's not in his room.
He was pretty upset.
Is that the cow that
died from last night?
Yeah.
I've never seen what things
look like on the inside before.
Is that what Tian-Chen looked like...
after what they did to her?
No, sweetie.
Everything's covered in snow,
and it looks so different outside.
I think she'd like that.
Hey, how about you and me...
I'm gonna go home.
Ethan?
She loved you.
Tian-Chen.
She loved you very much.
I know.
Excuse me....
When I worked at the diner,
one of the...
We used to try on dresses sometimes,
when things were slow.
We'd go to the storage and...
Well, it was silly.
But this was the one she always...
This one was her favorite.
She said she'd wear it the
day we all went home.
I just thought...
Thank you, Sara.
Thank you.
That's a heavy pour, even
on a day like today.
What I'm about to do...
I'm gonna do.
And that's it. I don't wanna talk.
I don't wanna listen.
Kenny, what are the bottles for?
I'm going into the tunnels.
I'm gonna find those things...
and I'm gonna burn every
last fucking one of them.
- You think that'll work?
- We burned the last one.
- The last one was already dead.
- I don't care.
I don't care.
I'm gonna make those
fucking things hurt.
- Okay.
- Okay what?
Okay. Let's do it.
Let's go.
Victor and Tabitha said they're,
everywhere down there.
Yet Jade went down there,
clearly saw some disturbing shit.
What he didn't see...
creatures, not a single one.
Do you still think they're down there?
I don't know.
Maybe they went somewhere else after
Tabitha and Victor found them
or maybe they went deeper in.
This is one thing I do know.
This is how they want us...
angry, stumbling around in the dark.
I also know this.
Hey, if we find them,
there's a good chance
we are not coming back.
But if this is what you want to do...
I will go with you, side by side,
and we will take out as many of
those motherfuckers as we can.
I can't stop thinking about...
how...
scared she must have been,
how alone she must have felt.
Hey.
She wasn't alone.
What?
They made me watch.
I couldn't help her. I couldn't...
But... Hey.
She was strong, Kenny.
- She was strong.
- No, no.
Listen, listen to me. She was brave.
She looked at me, and she did
not take her eyes off me.
And before...
before she died, she said...
You know, I don't even know
if I'm saying this right.
"Take care of him"...
that's what it means.
"Take care of him."
"He'll be alone now."
Come here. Come here, man. Come here.
It's okay.
I got you, brother.
Hey, let's go back, okay?
Let's go back.
Think her hair's okay?
Yeah, I think her hair is great.
What about the makeup? Do you think...
do you think her makeup's okay?
Honestly, I think if you try and
put any more makeup on her,
Tian-Chen might sit up and slap
the lipstick out of your hand.
I just... I just... I just
want it to be right for Kenny.
It's right.
Okay?
You'll come with us when we go.
I just wanted to say thank you
for what you did last night.
You're welcome.
Something happened to me a few days ago.
- I was...
- I heard. You okay?
No. No, not really.
I think this place has
gotten in my head now,
and I'm scared of what that might mean.
I don't want to hurt anybody.
- I don't...
- It's okay.
You can say it.
I don't wanna end up like you.
I wouldn't either.
If you ever want to talk...
Thanks.
Well, believe it or not, it
all started on my birthday.
See, me and Miranda were
hippies back in the day,
but we gave up all the drugs,
all the drinking when she
got pregnant with Victor.
Then, one day, years later,
it was my 35th birthday,
Miranda gets it in her head
that we're gonna take a
stroll down memory lane.
She gets us two hits of acid.
We take the kids to her
parents' house for the night,
and we take one last trip
for old times' sake.
That's when the voices started,
when she started seeing things.
She painted everything she saw.
Oh, my God.
I've seen that, too.
She said it was like she'd been chosen.
She said it was a place
that was everywhere,
but you couldn't find it if you tried.
Oh, my God.
Somewhere you could stumble
into from anywhere,
but never find a way to leave.
She said there were people there...
people who were lost...
and afraid...
who found themselves
living inside a nightmare
that they couldn't escape...
fighting a battle they
knew they couldn't win.
She said they were holding on to hope.
And when that hope was gone...
they held on to each other.
It all sounded like riddles,
gibberish.
She said that, of all the people
who would find their way to this place,
she was the one who had been
chosen to free the children.
But she wasn't the first.
Others were chosen before her.
She could see each and every one.
And all of them had failed.
None of them had ever
set the children free.
And none of them had ever gone home.
So, if you've seen the children,
if they've called to
you, then I guess...
you've been chosen now, too.
- So, how did you get out?
- Oh, my God.
How you holding up?
Dad.
Not good.
Look, I know you...
carry a lot of weight from this place,
and...
I know it feels like everything
that happens here...
We can't keep doing this.
We can't just keep sitting around,
waiting to see what...
- We need more information.
- Yeah.
- Yeah. - I'm gonna need your help
with something tomorrow.
Okay?
Yeah, all right. But with what?
We're gonna catch one of
these fucking things.
Are we still gonna live here?
Even though Tian-Chen is gone?
I don't know.
I have to take that one step at a time.
Are you not coming inside?
No, I'm gonna go check on the
animals, and make sure they're fed.
It's almost dark.
- Won't be long.
- I'm gonna go, too.
Well, just be careful.
Yeah, okay.
I love you guys.
Hello?
Dad?
It's Thomas.
www.subtitulamos.tv