Previously on From...
That's why you wanted a divorce.
'Cause it would be easier
for you to cut and run,
instead of trying to put
our family back together!
When you're with your wife,
you should shut the fuck up and listen.
What you're doing,
how tight you're holding
on to everything,
you're doing it because you're scared.
Ever since I woke up, something
has been happening to me.
I hear people screaming.
You're at a threshold. The
hero has to be brave.
Julie! Julie!
It was the boy in white.
He was the one that was telling
secrets to Christopher.
Christopher wouldn't
go to the tree, so...
What?
I told my mother what
the Boy in White said.
Help me, Elgin.
I can save all of you.
Is this really where it happens?
We were in the greenhouse.
She was trying to help me.
Oh, Fatima!
I said go!
I couldn't stop.
There is either something
horrible growing inside of her
or else this place has
finally broken her mind.
But if you are not gonna
tell everyone, then I am.
I'm gonna leave supplies for
you at the shack twice a week.
Fatima!
It's the only place that
the baby will be safe.
- There is no baby.
- Yes, there is.
It's just not yours.
Out of my way!
No! No, no! No! No, no!
Elgin!
Help!
Fatima!
Hey, it's getting dark.
I'm not going back to
town without her, Dad.
Listen, Ellis, she took the talisman.
So what? All right, she
wouldn't just leave.
We don't know that. Maybe she...
Hey, listen to me. Listen to me.
Look, we can come back out
in the morning, okay?
No, I'm not leaving her
out here overnight.
What are you gonna do? Huh?
You just gonna...
You just...
- What's wrong with your hand?
- Nothing.
Let's just...
let's just...
Dad.
- What's wrong?
- Okay.
What's wrong?
Okay, come here.
I got you.
Come on.
Yeah.
Watch it.
Hey.
I got you some things to help you
get a little more comfortable.
Elgin...
please, just let me go.
You're not a prisoner here.
I told you, this is for your own good.
Hey.
I'm trying to protect you.
Elgin, listen to me.
I saw her.
That thing that's been
speaking to you, I saw her.
What she's saying isn't true.
This thing inside me, it's not good.
It won't do good things. Look
at what happened to Tillie.
That happened because
the baby was scared.
- Elgin...
- It was hungry.
You weren't feeding it.
Fatima, you have to stop fighting.
Hey, hey, hey. You know,
wait, wait, wait.
Fatima, Fatima, Fatima, please.
Just listen. Listen. It's okay.
It's okay.
Just sit.
You need to eat. Yes.
The sooner you eat, the
stronger the baby will be,
and before you know it,
we'll be going home.
All of us.
The baby already helped us once.
The night I found out you were pregnant,
I remembered my dream,
and that helped Boyd save the town.
Elgin, no.
It's so hungry, Fatima.
- Just a little.
- No.
Please?
You helped me so much
since I first got here.
- Please let me help you.
- No.
Come on. Just a little bit.
See?
www.subtitulamos.tv
Hey, Victor.
I don't want to talk anymore.
I understand this could
be difficult for you.
But if what you remember
can help us understand
- what's happening...
- No, it won't!
I can't... I can't help you
'cause all I did is make things worse.
How?
She never would've gone...
if I... if I hadn't...
I don't want to remember anymore!
Come on, Victor.
No, I can't help you.
I can't help anyone.
I'm sorry.
What happened just now?
When you touched him?
I don't... I don't... I don't know.
Hey, you need to...
you need to get out to the clinic.
Something happened to
Julie out in the woods.
What?
Yeah.
Okay, and just look right here.
Gonna check your pupils.
Good.
Is she okay?
Well, I don't see any signs
of trauma, so that's good.
I'm telling you, I'm fine.
See? Nothing to worry about, okay?
Here.
- Drink this.
- Thanks.
Julie, can you walk me through
again exactly what happened?
There's not much to say.
We got to the ruins,
I walked inside, and then I blacked out.
You don't remember anything else?
I... I had a really weird dream.
That's all.
Okay, well, I'd like
to keep you overnight,
if that's okay with you.
- Yeah, yeah, that's fine.
- Yeah. Okay.
We'll give you folks some space.
Thank you.
What were you and Ethan doing out there?
It was stupid. We...
I went to the woods
yesterday with Randall
and then, we got to the ruins...
With...
You were out there with Randall?
- Look, Dad, it's not like that.
- Julie?
Hi, Mom.
- What happened? Are you okay?
- Yes. Yeah, I'm fine.
- I'll be right back.
- Okay.
What's wrong? Are you hurt?
No. I passed out a little.
- What do you mean, "a little"?
- It's okay.
Come on.
Randall, are you in there?
Something I can do for you?
What were you and Julie
doing out in the woods?
What did she say we were
doing in the woods?
I'm asking you.
Look, if this is your version
of the big bad dad routine,
I'm not in the fucking mood, all right?
After what happened with you
and Marielle and Julie...
She won't talk about it.
And I know she's going
through something that...
I cannot understand, but
I figured you might.
I was teaching her how to drive, man.
What?
She said she didn't have
her learner's permit,
so we boosted the Colony House van.
I freaked out about something
and we ended up in the woods.
And the ruins that you saw?
Look, man, I don't mean to be a dick,
but I got my own shit
going on, all right?
You want me to explain what
happened to us? Well, I can't.
And I don't know about
those fucking ruins,
but I told her not to go back out there.
Why?
Because they...
They just felt wrong.
How?
They just fucking did, Jim.
That's what I got.
Are we done?
You want my advice?
Go get the van and teach
your kid how to drive,
because there is fuck all
you can do about the rest.
None of us are getting
out of here alive.
I don't accept that.
It's good for you.
All right.
Yeah.
Take it easy.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
All right, we need to
get you to the clinic.
I said I'm fine.
Sun's going down.
I gotta ring that bell.
All right.
Okay. All right. Dad,
you can barely walk.
All right? You're not fine.
Whatever's going on with you...
I know what's going on with me!
What?
Fuck.
Yeah, I've known for a while.
Sit down.
Hey, Ellis, Ellis, Ellis.
She took the talisman.
Wherever she is, wherever
she went, she's safe.
Okay? Hey.
Sit down.
We need to talk.
Yeah.
We are here tonight
to celebrate a very special anniversary.
One year ago today...
our dear sweet Fatima
came into our lives.
Some of you were here then.
Many of you arrived since.
But all of you
have come to know her and to love her,
for her kindness,
for her strength,
for her wisdom...
And for her weed!
The green thumb is
definitely a big plus.
Our greenhouse never smelled so good.
Seriously, the truth is,
you've made this big old drafty box
feel a little bit more like home.
Happy anniversary, sweet pea.
The kids asleep?
Yeah.
Ethan finally conked out.
I could have stayed with Julie.
We should've have taken
Ethan back to the house.
And miss all the fun? Come on.
Who doesn't like a sleepover?
I haven't been doing a very good job.
Oh, Jim, it's okay. You...
Let me finish.
I know you're trying to
make sense of this place
and what happened.
And if there's even a chance that
it could lead us home, then...
then I'm in.
All the way.
No more second-guessing,
no more pushing back.
There's something
Julie's not telling us.
I know.
How long have you known?
It started just before I went
out into the woods with Sara.
Anyone else know?
Yeah. Kristi.
Kenny.
- I didn't want to worry you.
- You should've told me.
I'm telling you now.
Has that happened before?
Yeah, with your leg.
No.
So, it's getting worse.
Seems like it, yeah.
There's something...
something else I need to tell you.
What?
When I was in the barn with Tian-Chen...
they made me watch.
They made me...
watch her die.
The whole thing was a set-up to...
They said they wanted to break me.
Jesus.
What if this thing with Fatima,
with the baby...
No, Dad, this isn't...
this isn't because of you.
But you don't know that. You don't.
We don't know a fucking thing,
and now Tillie is dead,
and Fatima is out there
somewhere, and...
and I'm sitting here
like a fucking gimp.
You doing okay in there, Boyd?
Fuck.
What'd you say?
Dad, no.
- Hey, Dad.
- Hey, no. Stop.
You shut your fucking mouth.
- Shut your fucking mouth!
- Dad!
- Come on, Dad, just...
- Oh, you want...
- Get away from the fucking window.
- Fuck!
All right, all right. All right.
What?
No.
No, stop it! Stop it!
No!
No, no, no, no, no!
No, stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
Leave me alone!
Look at you.
I told you when you started to
eat, things would go faster.
The baby's gonna be here in no time.
You know, you should
probably put this on.
Those aren't going to fit you soon.
I hope it's okay.
I had to go to the main storage.
I didn't want to risk
going into your room.
Can you help me get up?
Yeah. Of course.
No, no! No, Fatima, stop!
Elgin! No, no! Stop! Elgin!
Help! Help! Help!
You can't go out there blind.
She could be anywhere.
I'm not gonna find her
just staying here.
Okay, then, we get more people.
- Get a search party.
- How?
How? Donna is about to tell the
entire town what Fatima did.
You really think that people are gonna be
lining up to help when they hear about that?
I will talk to Donna.
- Okay, great. Let me know how that goes.
- Ellis! Listen!
Sorry.
I didn't mean to interrupt,
but I don't think this can wait.
It's okay. What's going on?
Is Fatima okay?
She's missing, isn't she?
What the fuck do you know about that?
- No, what the fuck do you...
- Hey! Hey, hey!
That's enough.
Back up.
What happened?
It's okay.
I heard the voices last night
for the first time since the ruins.
What'd they say?
That Fatima didn't leave on her own,
that something took her.
Wait. What?
They want you to know that she's close.
She's afraid.
They were laughing.
- Why?
- Because...
they know you won't find her in time.
They want you to know
you can't save her.
What the fuck?
What the hell is he doing? Jesus Christ.
Victor? Victor! What are you doing?
All these things...
I kept all these things because
I thought they could help!
But all they do is hurt!
I want it gone! I want all of it gone!
Victor... Wait, just...
just wait! Hold on a second. Victor!
- Whoa, hey. What's going on?
- Get out of my way.
Not until you calm down.
- I said, get out of my way!
- Okay, yeah. Yeah.
Victor!
- Wait, wait, wait, wait!
- Hey!
Victor!
Victor, what's going on? Hey! What...
- What the hell?
- Victor!
Jesus.
Just put that down.
- I'm not gonna hurt anyone.
- Okay, fine.
Then put it down.
I need it.
- You're scaring people.
- No.
They should be scared.
They're... no one's scared enough.
- Victor, please.
- I was...
I was so stupid!
Yeah, I'm gonna...
Just... let me go, please. Please!
If you tell us what
you need the axe for.
I'm gonna go chop down a tree.
I'm just gonna go back to the house.
No, come on. You need to
eat something. Come on.
Hey, guys.
Nice to see the place
up and running again.
I had a little help.
This guy helped a lot with the
cleaning and the reorganizing.
You know, any time you wanna
come and lend a hand,
I could always use a helper.
Well, you hear that?
You know, Kenny was really supportive.
I think it was hard for him
to see this place empty all the time.
And after what happened to Tillie,
I think people need a
place that feels normal.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, of course.
Did they find who did it to her?
Not yet.
Just... eat.
- Yeah.
- Grab something.
- I'll get us a couple of plates.
- Yeah.
Busy.
It's Boyd.
Come in.
Look, look, I know you're upset with me,
- but there's something that...
- I'm not gonna say anything...
about what Fatima did
because of what she
means to people here...
her spirit, her light.
I don't think people could take it.
I don't think I can take it.
She's gone.
What?
I had her in that shed
just outside of town.
Ellis and I went there last night
and she was gone.
She left?
Those voices that Sara hears?
They said something took her.
That she's close by,
but we won't be able to save
her before it's too late.
She said the voices were laughing.
Fuck this place.
Ring the bell. We'll call a meeting.
What can I get you?
What? You don't like your food?
I miss Tian-Chen's pancakes.
- Hey, where you going?
- I'm going to the bathroom.
He thinks it's his fault,
what happened to me.
Why would he?
Because I asked him what I should do,
if I should go inside the ruins or not.
I know it was stupid. I just...
it felt so much like one of those
stories he always used to tell us,
and I was afraid, and I
didn't know who else to ask.
And no offense, but this whole
"perfect family breakfast" thing,
I know what you're trying
to do, but it's...
it's not making anything better.
It's just making everything worse.
Everybody!
- Come on.
- Come on!
- What's going on?
- I don't know.
We're gonna need everyone
to come outside a minute.
Come on. Let's go.
- Mom?
- Come on.
- What's happening?
- You guys go.
- I'll wait for Ethan.
- Okay.
Fill in. Over here.
Dad, what are you doing?
It's okay.
We're okay.
Come on over.
All right, everyone, listen up.
What happened to Tillie,
we know you're all scared.
We know you want answers.
I want answers too.
But right now, we don't have them.
What's going on?
- We called you all here because...
- Come on. Everybody's outside.
Look, we need your help.
That's...
Hey.
Fatima is missing.
- What?
- Fatima's missing?
Nobody's...
nobody's seen her since last night.
What we're asking for is a search party.
People to scour the town, every corner,
every crack, so we can bring her home.
Whatever took her, is
that what killed Tillie?
We don't know.
Look, I don't have all the
information on what happened.
All I know is that she's close by.
How do you know that?
I know that because
something here told us,
something that wants us to know
that she's alone, that she's afraid.
Something that thinks that
we don't have what it takes
to find her.
Now, look, I can't tell
anybody what to do.
Right? But...
you see these here?
We didn't always have these.
When I first got here,
those things in the woods,
they would come out at night
and they would take whoever
the fuck they wanted.
Everybody here was living day to day,
moment to moment, hour to hour.
We found these.
We proved that this place
couldn't break us.
Now it's trying to break us again.
So you can either lay down and die or...
we can say fuck you.
Fuck you!
We are taking our lives back!
It's possible to fight back!
We proved it once before
and I am asking for your help
to prove it again.
Now, look, it's your choice.
There's no shame in backing out.
Okay?
How are we gonna do this?
Great.
We're gonna...
We're gonna pair up.
We're all gonna go out
there in groups of two,
and we're gonna cover every
inch of this place, okay?
Okay.
Okay. Let's do it. Let's go.
I have to help. Fatima's my friend.
I wanna help too.
All right. I'll take Ethan.
- Okay.
- You take Julie.
We'll cover more ground that way.
Yeah. Okay.
Be careful.
You too. Come on.
Ellis.
Hey.
There are gonna be a lot of questions.
Best if one of us finds her.
We've got a better chance
by splitting up. Okay?
Okay.
Hey.
We are going to find her.
Yeah.
Kenny!
- Yeah. - Hey, you mind
coming out there with me?
Yeah, of course.
- Great.
- Okay.
Let's go.
Ellis.
You need someone to search with?
Yeah, I'd appreciate that.
Anything I can do to help.
Fatima! Can you hear me?!
I don't understand what
we're doing out here.
No one's forcing you to help.
- You wanna go back to Colony House...
- That's not what I...
Look, Boyd said that something told
you guys that she was out here.
- What does that even mean?
- That part came from Sara.
Fatima!
Sara? The girl who murdered people.
She's connected to this place
in ways that are hard to understand.
So, you're just gonna
take her word for it?
What if Sara killed Tillie and Fatima
and then just made up some bullshit
about Fatima being held captive
in the woods somewhere?
That's not what happened.
How do you know?
I just do.
Okay. So, then, why
wouldn't this magical voice
just tell Sara where Fatima is?
Better yet, why not tell
her who killed Tillie?
That's not the way it works, okay?
So, then, tell me how it fucking works.
You know something.
You know something that
you're not telling me.
I don't understand you people.
I'm a good cop.
I can be an asset here, if you just...
If I what? If I walk you through
the many different ways
this place will fuck with your head?
I don't have time for a
goddamn tutorial, okay?
Fatima is out there.
We need to find her.
Because of what she means
to the people of this town.
Because of what she means to me.
If you want me to believe that
you are good at your job,
I need you to trust me.
I need you to help me.
Can you do that?
Yeah.
Good.
When this is over, we'll talk, okay?
Okay.
Fatima!
Hey, so, you're up at
Colony House now, huh?
Yep.
I been meaning to come up there
and look in on you. I just...
It's fine. You've got...
You got bigger things to
worry about right now.
Yeah, always are bigger things.
Yeah.
Hey, Kenny.
Look, I realize, you and me...
things are never gonna
be the same again.
- Boyd, we don't have to...
- No, I...
I lied to you about what Sara did,
about your Dad, and I know
there's a part of you
that's never gonna forgive me.
Being in charge of this
place, it comes with a...
whole mess of decisions you
never really want to make.
But people live and die here
based on your ability to
make those decisions.
What are you doing?
It's getting worse.
Parkinson's.
Yesterday my leg froze. I almost...
couldn't stand.
- Jesus, I...
- Look.
I'm not saying it's today, okay?
Or tomorrow or a month from now.
But I got a clock ticking on me.
Yesterday, that clock started
ticking a little faster.
So...
I need to know that, when I'm gone...
- No, I'm not...
- Look!
I need to know that when I'm gone
or when I'm too goddamn
feeble to do anything,
I need to know that
you are gonna step up
and look after this place.
It has to be you wearing this badge
and not some hothead like Acosta
or anybody else who might
come through here.
You.
I need to know that my family
is in good hands.
I'm not taking your badge.
Kenny...
But...
if you're still looking for a deputy,
I'll take that one back.
Okay?
Yeah?
Yeah.
Come on. Let's keep looking.
Fatima!
Okay. Here we go.
What the fuck do you want, huh?
You think at this point, I haven't
seen enough of you people?
Try something new 'cause this... this,
it's not doing it for me anymore.
You okay? Who are you talking to?
Nobody.
Well, let me rephrase that:
who did you think you were talking to?
Henry, I'm busy. All right?
What do you want?
You did this?
I did, yeah.
My wife made one of these in our yard.
So you keep telling me.
What's it for?
I don't know, okay? I
thought it might help.
Help figure out those numbers, you mean?
Is there something I can help you with?
Most of the town's out
looking for that girl.
What?
The sheriff's daughter-in-law.
We had a whole meeting about it.
Didn't you hear the bell?
Yeah, I just, I'm...
You were busy.
Right, yeah.
You wanna come help me look?
- Listen, I...
- I was hoping we could talk
about Victor.
Stop!
You can't do that.
It's a bad tree. It does bad things.
It's important.
Why?
Why is it important?
Why... why won't you help us?!
Because I tried.
With Christopher.
I think you need to
learn for yourselves.
It's the only way you'll understand.
You look different now.
So do you.
All those years, you looked the same.
Why are you changing now?
Everything's changing now.
Is that bad?
'Cause I don't know what to do.
You tell me...
You tell me how I can help them.
Please.
You're supposed to be my friend.
I am your friend.
Then help me.
Please? Please help me.
Just tell me what to do.
Don't cut down that tree.
Where are you going?
No, come back!
Come back!
Where are you going?
You know, when I was little,
a friend of mine went missing.
You wanna talk about panic?
We had the whole neighborhood
out looking for him.
Grandma said not to worry,
but I was so scared.
Turns out he's on a playground
on the other side of town,
having the time of his life.
Everyone was scared for nothing.
Is that what you think this is?
Everybody's scared for nothing?
No.
I just...
I think sometimes we think the worst
when we really don't know.
Okay, well, what we do know
is that my wife is missing.
All right, no offense. We're not looking
for some fucking kid on a playground.
I already lost my mom.
If something happens to Fatima...
Your mom was here?
Look, when she died...
the way she died...
I can't go through that again.
I won't.
You think she could be in there?
Well, you never know.
Best to check everywhere.
Besides, I think this'll
be a good place to talk.
About what?
Come on inside.
What happened to the window?
Well, we had a bit of a close
call not too long ago.
Doesn't look like Fatima's in here.
I know.
Last time you were in here,
you were in pretty bad shape.
And all I remember thinking
was, "It's my fault."
"I was the one who was driving."
"I was the one who didn't
see the other car coming."
I just kept thinking we
were gonna lose you,
right then and there,
just like we lost Thomas.
And I never would have forgiven myself.
But it wasn't your fault.
No?
Why not?
Well, because you were scared
and you were doing the best you could.
Kinda like you were when you told
Julie to go into those ruins?
You were doing the
best you could, right?
I guess.
Listen to me.
Things happen here,
things we can't control.
This place wants us to blame ourselves.
It wants us to be scared.
You have to remember that
we're all doing our best,
even when bad things happen,
especially when bad things happen.
Because how we face those
things, that's what matters.
Not the decisions we make
or whose fault it was, but how
we take care of each other
and how we always do our
best, no matter what.
You understand?
I love you, buddy.
I love you too, Dad.
So, what do you say
we keep looking, huh?
Dad? Are you there?
Dad, please, don't leave me alone here.
Come on, Dad.
You were right.
It's not him.
It's not Thomas.
Where are you going?
Dad.
What is this?
Victor comes here sometimes.
This is where we spent the night
when we came out of the tunnels.
- She's not here.
- Yeah.
Is this how it's gonna be from now on?
One by one, people just disappear?
No.
She was the first person who
made it seem like this place
might actually be okay.
Oh, honey, we're gonna find her.
Don't worry. Come on.
I don't think I was dreaming.
What?
When I blacked out in the ruins.
It was almost like I went somewhere.
Like,
one second I'm in this weird chamber
and the three of us are there...
me, Randall, and Marielle,
and we were screaming.
And then, there was this
guy chained to a wall,
and then I'm in these tunnels,
and I heard you talking to Victor.
I tried to find you, but your voice,
it kept just getting
further and further away.
And then I heard those children.
They were screaming that word.
Anghkooey.
All I kept thinking was,
"What if I never make it back?"
"What if... What if I'm lost
and no one ever finds me?"
No.
- "What if I'm alone now?"
- No.
- I was just so scared.
- Honey.
You're not alone.
You'll never, never be alone here.
Okay?
Come here.
What is it?
It's one of them watching us.
The children?
Yeah.
What is it doing?
She wants us to follow her.
Follow her where?
I don't know. Come on.
Everything about who Victor is now,
what he's been through,
I feel like I'm starting over
with a whole different person.
Well, yeah, it's 'cause you are.
Look, why are you talking
to me about this?
Why not Tabitha or...
I don't know, literally anybody else.
Tabitha's got her own
kids to worry about.
And don't take this the wrong way,
but you remind me of him.
I remind you of Victor?
A little.
He's off, trying to make a
block of wood tell a story,
and you're up on a ladder,
screaming at people who aren't there.
Okay, that's fair.
How would it be for you
if your dad showed up here
and saw you like this?
What would you want him to say to you?
Well, for starters, I'd want to know
where the fuck he's been my whole life,
but that's, that's... Listen, I...
You're trying to figure out
how to fix him, right?
You can't
'cause he's not broken.
Victor is the product of
what this place made him.
Victor has been surviving
here for decades.
He's been shaped by this place. He's...
He's Tarzan, growing up in the jungle.
And you're the guy who comes along
and makes him feel like an asshole
'cause he doesn't know
how to use a fork.
It's not rocket science.
Where are you going?
Back to the bar.
At least there I can pretend
I'm being productive.
Fatima!
You know she brought me here?
She was my proxy.
She helped me out a lot
since I first got here.
She's helped a lot of people.
It's what she does.
I'm so sorry about what
happened to your mom.
Forget about it.
You're not going to lose Fatima.
It's not gonna come to that.
- She's gonna be okay.
- Okay, would you just...
Just stop.
Please.
All right, I appreciate
you being out here.
I just can't...
I have to tell you something.
What?
When we were on the bus on
our way here, I had a dream.
Yeah, I remember.
And ever since then,
I feel like something has
been trying to talk to me.
What do you mean?
What if all this...
What if all of this is
happening for a reason?
What if Fatima is out there right now,
doing something to help us?
This might be a good thing, you know.
The baby and everything.
Wait. Why would this have
anything to do with the baby?
No, I'm just... trying to say that...
maybe...
we don't have all the information yet,
that's all.
I don't want you to be afraid.
I really...
I think she's gonna be okay.
Come on.
Let's keep looking.
Where are we going?
I don't know. They've
never done this before.
- Come on, come on, come on.
- I'm coming.
What do you want? What
do you want from me?!
No! No, no, no.
No, no, no! No, stay away from me.
Stay away from me. Stay away from me.
Stay away from me.
Stay away from me. No, no.
No! No!
No!
Where is she?
Hey. That's... that's the root cellar.
That's the one I stayed in when
Victor pushed me through the tree.
Someone's down there.
Hello?
Just stay here, okay?
Mom?
I'm okay.
Victor?
What are you doing here, Victor?
This is where it happened.
This is where she left us.
Not fair.
All those years I thought there was
a reason, a reason that I lived.
I was the reason she died.
No, Victor.
It wasn't your fault.
You were just a little boy.
I love you.
I love you so much.
No, no, no!
- What's wrong?
- No, no.
- No, no, no, no.
- Mom, what?
No, no, that's impossible.
- What...
- That's impossible.
No!
Mom!
Mom, what?
Don't touch me! Don't touch me!
- Mom, please, you're scaring me.
- Don't touch me!
Mom, Mom!
Please, how can I help you, Mom?
www.subtitulamos.tv