Synced & corrected by QueenMaddie
www.addic7ed.com
Previously, on From...
Is Daddy coming home?
Any second now.
You go start saying your prayers.
I'll be there in a minute.
- Meagan, what are you doing?
- Maybe I can come in.
Meagan, no!
You want a drink, huh?
- Get the...
- No.
A man protects his family, Frank.
Open your eyes and look!
Look at what you did. Look at them.
No!
Tell my parents I said goodbye.
Mom, Julie killed Norman.
- What happened to Norman?
- The monsters killed them.
There's no such thing
as monsters, honey.
Why is there a tree in
the middle of the road?
Must've gotten knocked down
in a storm or something.
Oh, this can't be the same place.
Excuse me?
We're trying to get back
onto the highway. Could you...
We're on the same fucking road.
Dad, I think he's bleeding.
There's something in his leg.
Are you a doctor?
I was a third-year medical student.
Please stop. It hurts. Ow!
We can make it to Colony House.
Run as fast as you can,
no matter what you see.
No matter what you
hear, you do not stop.
Hey, I need help here!
Hey. Hey! Donna, let us in!
You're from one of those two cars?
That hasn't happened
in a long, long time.
What do you think it means?
There are things you need
to know about where you are.
This, unfortunately, is gonna
be the worst conversation
of your life.
Do you believe in monsters?
Why did you bring me here?
'Cause I wanted you to
see that if you climb
high enough, even a nightmare
can look like a dream.
- This isn't your fault.
- What do you mean?
I hear their voices.
They said it was the
only way to go home.
Sara, just tell me what you did.
I left the door open.
Those things. They walk.
They never run.
They know there's only
so many places we can go.
I feel like I'm hanging
on by a thread here.
I can't find any more bodies.
- What are you looking at?
- Nothing.
- Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
- Come on! Come on!
Open the damn door!
You have a bad dream?
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
Tobey!
Somebody get me out of
this fucking thing. Hey!
- Tobey, where are you?
- What's going on?
Anybody fucking... Hey.
Shut the fuck up. People
are trying to sleep.
- Who the fuck are you?
- Sorry.
I'm usually more cordial when I do this.
You picked one hell of a
time to finally wake up.
Listen. I don't know
what's going on here,
alright, but you get me
outta these fucking straps
right fucking now, or
I swear to God I'm...
What?
Do you have any idea who I am?
Oh, shit. You're one of those.
One of what?
Okay.
Let's start at the beginning.
You hungry, Frank?
Anything you need?
Look.
It's important for
you to understand that
what happens tonight...
it's not personal.
I know.
She liked you.
Lauren.
She always liked you.
She said you were hard on
people 'cause you had to be.
That you made the decisions
other people couldn't.
You're the one who was
gonna get everybody home.
I wasn't always like this, you know.
None of us were.
Look.
If there's anything you need,
anyone you wanna see, maybe,
tie up loose ends...
There is one thing I'd like to do.
So, you're telling me that right now
I'm in a town I can't leave,
and that every night
when the sun goes down,
monsters come from
the forest to hunt us?
Monsters who, incidentally,
killed my friend the other night.
Yeah.
Fuck off.
This is... this is something.
Where did he... where did he find you?
Who?
Tobey. Are you guys individual hires,
or is this one of those
traveling companies?
'Cause, I mean, you play
the whole thing pretty great.
I buy it.
Not him so much. I just...
I thought you were trying
a little bit too hard.
But otherwise, I...
Bravo. Oh. Money well spent.
So, uh, okay.
So, what's next? Is there, uh...
Is there, like, some kind
of puzzle I have to solve?
Mmm.
Actually, you know what? Never mind.
- Don't spoil it for me.
- Where are you going?
Well, I'm not gonna solve the puzzle
sitting here all day.
I'm gonna, you know, check out the town,
turn over a few stones.
Fuck. Fuckin' Tobey.
This must have cost a fortune.
You want me to keep an eye on him?
No.
Let him wander around town for a while.
We got enough to deal with here.
Ha.
Okay.
It's not quite my Giacometti,
but, uh, it'll do.
Oh, perfect!
Is that for me?
Excuse me?
Hey. Do you, uh... do you
have anything motorized,
- like a scooter or something?
- What? No.
No? Okay. This'll do. Thank you.
I... No, that's my... Uh...
Hey, buddy.
Can I go outside today?
Oh, honey.
You need to stay in bed a little longer.
I'm tired of staying in bed.
And I don't like these pajamas.
They're itchy and they don't fit right.
Oh, come on.
Your dad went to
the RV to get our stuff.
So tonight you're gonna
sleep in your own pajamas.
We all should've gone.
Well, we thought it was
best if Dad went on his own.
Well, I don't like people
going through my stuff.
Nobody's gonna do that.
Yeah, okay.
How long are we gonna be here?
We are, uh... we're figuring that out.
Hey. You hungry?
I saw they're making eggs.
Do you want some eggs?
Hobo eggs?
No. No, no, no. No hobo eggs.
But they have oatmeal.
Okay.
What about you? You hungry?
Uh, no. I think I'm
just gonna go for a walk.
- Okay. Stay close.
- Yeah.
I am going to get you your oatmeal.
Stay there.
_
Oh, jeez.
You okay?
Here. Let me get that.
One...
three...
four, five.
Berries?
I'm okay.
There's an apple tree out
back if you'd prefer that.
I see you grow your own food.
Supermarkets around
here are terrible, so...
Oh.
You're joking.
Ellis and your dad
are gonna be back soon.
You'll feel a lot better
once you have some of your own things.
Yeah, I guess.
Hey.
You doing okay?
No. Not really.
Come here.
All right.
Let's see what we got here, bud.
I heard you were getting
a little itchy, so...
Thank you, Dad.
You're welcome.
Um, how did it go?
It was, uh... it was good.
Yeah?
Are my books in there?
Oh.
Books! How did I forget books?
Dad...
Oh, let's see. Maybe there's one.
Maybe I can find something.
Oh, wait a minute. We have books.
What do we want?
Do we want Adventures
of the Grand Gooligog?
Flight of the Cromenockle?
Ah. The Cromenockle.
That's my favorite.
Make the sound.
Make the sound? I have no idea
what you're even... doo-ooh!
She doesn't sound like that.
No? Does it sound like...
No. Stop. Stop it.
Okay, okay, okay.
There's gonna be two
Cromenockles for you.
Two.
Two Cromenockles for the cave.
Two Cromenockles for you.
Careful with your leg.
Julie, look. We got our stuff.
Yeah. So I see.
- Hey, come here.
- Julie!
We're reading the Cromenockle.
Julie!
- Yeah. It's really funny.
- Hey.
Uh, sorry to interrupt.
Father Khatri is here
to talk to you about
the choosing ceremony.
What's the choosing ceremony?
I'll let him fill you in.
All newcomers have to decide
where they're gonna live.
Here in Colony House
or down in the town.
It's just part of how we do things here.
I'd like to take the both
of you, show you around.
Maybe take you to the
house you'd be staying in,
should you choose the town.
Well, I wanna come.
What? This is about all of us, right?
I wanna see.
We need you to stay
here and be with Ethan.
Donna can watch Ethan.
Okay. Fine.
You guys go ahead.
Hey.
We won't be gone long.
Okay.
You know what?
Maybe I should stay.
I shouldn't leave her alone.
I think it's very important
that both of you see this.
It's gonna be okay.
She's a tough kid.
Takes after her mother.
Come.
Good morning, everybody.
What's cooking today, huh?
Is this where I find my next clue?
Is this where the, uh...
Is this where the monsters
jump from the shadows?
Uh, "Oh, what wonders
will avail themselves
in the quaint little roadside diner
in which my guard hath fallen?"
Huh?
I did some summer stock back in the day.
Not bad, right? Oh,
thank you. I'm starving.
- What've we got?
- Hey. There's a line.
Look. I'm all for authenticity,
but I'm also really hungry,
and since y'all basically
work for me anyways,
it's kind of okay.
Ow. What the...
All right. Jeez.
People really take all this seriously.
What are you doing here?
You promised you'd stay home.
If I didn't show up, they
would have wondered why.
It'll be okay. I wanna help.
- Sara...
- I need to help.
You should get back to the barn.
- It'll be okay.
- Sara...
I promise.
It's the talismans
that keep them out.
Now, there are a number of
other precautions people take.
Nailing the windows shut, for instance.
With a child in the
house, this is a must.
Why?
Well, there'll be nights
where these... these things,
they'll try to convince
you to let them in.
And children tend to
be most susceptible.
How are people walking around
like all this is normal?
Well, the people who survive here
are the ones who adapt.
How exactly do they do that?
The way someone who lives
on a fault line, for example.
They adapt to the notion
that the earth could just open up
and swallow them at any given moment.
They go on with their lives
because that reality is a part
of the world that they live in.
Look. I wish there was an
explanation I could give you
that would make any of this easier.
But it's gonna be fine.
Okay? Just always remember.
Place the talisman by the
door. Cover your windows.
Nail your windows shut.
You do these things, your
family's going to be just fine.
Hey. Um, I'm sorry. What's that?
Um, we call that the box.
It's our only form of
punishment we have here.
You see, the rules we live by
are meant to protect each other,
to keep each other safe.
And when someone's actions or negligence
leads to the death
of a resident in town,
the only punishment for that
crime is a night in the box.
Jesus.
But you keep one of those
talismans in there, right?
No.
How many times have you used it?
Tonight will be the first.
Look. Come.
- Your house is just up ahead.
- Yeah.
So, it's not much, but
it'll keep you comfortable
if you choose to live in town.
Looks like somebody's
already living here.
Um, there was a...
There was an incident the
night before you arrived.
The first we'd had in months.
What kind of incident?
The kind that happens
when people are careless.
It was a child?
Holy fuck.
Meagan, and her mother Lauren.
The father was passed out drunk
at the other end of
town when it happened.
This is what happens
when you break the rules.
Tabitha, wait.
No, Jim, I'm sorry. I can't.
I can't do that right now.
You make it seem like we have a choice.
Jim.
Jim, this is fucking insane!
That woman and her little
girl were ripped apart.
Now they're putting the dad
in some fucking box at sundown
for those things to...
You heard what the priest said.
If he'd have followed the rules,
they'd all still be alive right now.
Jim? Why are you... Why are you so eager
to take any of this at face value, Jim?
Because I can still hear
those things whispering
outside the RV.
I can still hear them
tapping on the glass.
Tabby, whatever this is,
it's real, and we are stuck.
So we better figure out
a way to make the best of it.
'Cause we don't want to end up like...
No, no, no. No.
This was Meagan's favorite spot.
Put this swing here for her,
and she was always wanting me
to push her higher and higher,
but Lauren was afraid it wasn't safe.
You'll bury me next to them, right?
Yeah.
Of course.
Okay.
I'll just be a few minutes here.
Okay. Take whatever time you need.
All right, little guy.
Give that a try and let
me know how it feels.
Feel good?
It hurts my armpit.
Oh, it hurts your armpit? Okay. Hold on.
Here. I'll add a little
extra padding there for you,
and if this feels good,
I'll tie it on later, okay?
Here. Try that.
Ready? Here.
Let's go down the stairs, yeah.
Take your time. There you go, buddy.
Come on. Three, two, one.
Boom!
He's adorable.
Why are you doing this?
What do you mean?
You guys barely know us.
It's just what we do.
It's, like, the ultimate escape room.
I mean, seriously, I don't know
how he pulled all this together.
So, um, I'm thinking
maybe there's a clue in
each one of the buildings?
Hmm? Am I getting warmer?
'Cause I mean, usually, you know,
you have some type of
prompt that lets you know
which direction to
go. But this is, uh...
This is just some next-level shit.
Has, uh...
Has anyone talked to you yet?
Yeah. The lady up at
the, uh, big house. Donna.
I mean, she gave me the whole intro.
You know, the monsters in the forest.
Tobey's dead. Blah, blah, blah.
But she didn't give me any hints
about where I'm supposed to go
next. Here's the thing, though.
Like, as thorough as all this feels,
there's a couple flaws in the logic.
I'm sitting here eating eggs in a diner
in a place that's supposed to be, what,
some kind of mystical nightmare?
I mean, I don't know about you,
but my nightmares don't
usually serve breakfast.
I suppose you're gonna
tell me you've got chickens
roaming around in the big bad forest?
Yeah, but the chickens, the cows?
We don't really know
where they come from.
Mmm.
That's actually not bad
for a nightmare breakfast.
I should probably get going.
Am I supposed to get anything from you?
What?
I don't know. Like a clue
or some kind of cryptic direction?
You know what?
Never mind. I'll figure it out.
Thanks.
- Was that...
- The guy from the other car.
He's gonna get himself killed.
Um, are you hungry? Have
you eaten anything yet?
No, I'm fine. I just came
to check on you guys.
Right.
Okay.
How's she doing?
Well, she's...
Uh, like I said, denial is a
major part of our family tree.
Let's see, now.
Twelve.
Ten, 12.
Okay.
What are you doing?
I don't think you're
supposed to be out here.
Are you looking for something?
Go away.
I can help you look. I'm
good at finding stuff.
I'm not looking.
I'm checking.
What are you checking?
You ask a lot of questions.
That was only three.
- I can help you check.
- No.
No, you're trouble.
Your mom or pop comes back
and they see you out
here, who gets blamed?
And Donna cuts me off.
Then no more peaches.
- What are you talking about?
- Just go away.
Have you seen the boy
who lives out here?
- What?
- Forget it.
No, no. Hold on.
What do you mean "lives out here"?
He's always walking around out here,
and I never see him inside.
So I figured he lived
out here somewhere.
Is that right?
We're friends.
Are you, now?
Well, it's good to have friends.
Okay.
Wait. Hey, come here.
I'm checking to see if they've moved.
If what moved?
The trees.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Did they?
Don't know yet. I'm not done checking.
Ethan?
Ethan, what the fuck?
Get back inside. Mom
told me to watch you.
Guess I gotta go.
Yeah. I guess you'd better, then.
Will you let me know about the trees?
I'll keep you looped.
Ethan, now.
Hey.
If you see that friend of yours,
tell him Victor says hello.
Don't talk to him.
Why?
Because he's creepy.
- No, he's not.
- Come on.
He's checking to see if the trees moved.
Yeah, and that's totally normal.
One, two.
Yahtzee. All right, Tobey.
Let's see what you got.
Holy shit.
What the fuck?
Tobey, you're a fucking genius!
Ah. Woo!
That's a sight I don't see very often.
Yeah, well...
Don't get used to it.
He's not answering.
Well, perhaps you're not
listening closely enough.
I can't do it.
Frank. The box.
Can't do it.
It was never supposed...
I built the goddamn box as a deterrent.
It's supposed to scare people.
I... can't.
All right.
Let's say you don't.
Let's say you absolve
Frank of all his crimes.
Then what?
What happens next time?
I mean, you warned him
on several occasions.
Very publicly, I might add.
How do you think people are gonna react
when you let Frank go?
How much weight do you think the rules
that hold this town together will carry?
Aren't you supposed to be talking to me
about the virtues of mercy?
I see.
Is that what you'd prefer?
Hey. I'd prefer not to put
a broken man in a fucking box
to be torn apart when the sun goes down!
That's what I'd prefer.
I'm not gonna stand
here and pretend like
this is an easy decision.
Great.
But you built a guillotine
in the town square.
What do you think happens
when people realize
you lack the conviction to use it?
You're a terrible fucking priest.
You know that?
Fucking worst.
Now I'm cursing in
the house of the Lord.
What the fuck is this?
Goddamn it!
There's a little shack
about a hundred yards
beyond the tree line.
You take that, you put
it next to the door,
and you make whatever
life you can out there.
What are you gonna tell everybody?
Thank you all for coming.
Today, our newcomers will
choose where they would like
to spend their days here with us.
Should you choose to spend your time
with the people of the town
to live by our rules for
the good of the community
until we find our way back home,
you will select the rock.
Should you choose to join
with the people of Colony House
to live for today because
tomorrow is not guaranteed,
you will select the flower.
Now, once you have chosen,
this choice will be final.
- Like many of us here...
- Father Khatri?
Uh, sorry. Do you mind if I, uh...
Uh, yeah. Sure.
Since we're all gathered here,
figure I might as well address
the elephant in the room.
Been a lot of questions
today about Frank, the box,
the rules.
There is a fine line
between savagery and consequence.
And if we're not willing...
Frank?
I'd like to say a few
things, if that's all right.
You know what I've been thinking
about these last couple of days,
sitting in my cell?
Christmas.
The last one me and Lauren
and Meagan had before we...
I was a good dad, you know?
I mean, I wasn't perfect,
but I wasn't like this.
That last Christmas, we got
Meagan her first dollhouse.
And when she saw it,
the look on her face...
I let this town,
those things in the woods,
I let them get to my head, and...
I forgot what really mattered.
I... forgot that if I'd just been
a little stronger...
there might have still
been a Christmas morning
waiting for us all when we got home.
Don't let this place
take that away from you.
Okay?
You look after each other.
You take care of each other.
Remember what you're living for.
I appreciate everything you're
trying to do for me, Sheriff.
No, I do. I really do.
But the only two things that
I love in this world are gone.
And I just wanna see my girls again.
Wait! No! Don't go, Frank.
Goddamn, I love this! It's scary.
It's, uh, dramatic. It's...
Okay. Whoa, big fella. Okay.
All right, okay. Easy, easy.
- Easy.
- Pick one.
You need to fucking let
me go. Ow! What the fuck?
- Pick one!
- I'm gonna fucking sue you.
Ow! Okay. All right. Okay.
- All right. All right?
- Got it.
Let's go.
Damn it! Ow! Damn! Ah!
Oh, you have no idea how
badly you just fucked up, okay?
All right? No idea.
I am gonna... I'm gonna
fucking ruin you.
All right, I'm gonna
fucking ruin all of you!
Jade, let me show you something.
Come on.
Frank, you don't have to do this.
You shouldn't be making decisions
like this when you're hurting.
No. Look. I'm the most clear-minded
I've been in a long time. Trust me.
All right.
Let's get this done.
Are you living in town or Colony House?
Town.
Sorry.
You each have to say it.
Oh, yeah. Town.
Ethan.
Town.
Okay.
Julie.
Colony House.
- What? No, no.
- No. She doesn't mean that.
Girl made her choice.
- Hold on a second.
- It's done.
- Ceremony is over.
- No, no, I'm sorry.
She can't make that
decision. She's underage.
- No.
- Mom, it's fine.
No, it's not fine. Come
and stay with your family.
You don't have to do that, Julie.
I'm not talking to you.
I'm talking to my daughter.
Now, there's no way anyone's
gonna expect us to...
Are you gonna say something?
Okay. Everybody just hold on, okay?
Take a breath.
Ju... Julie, Julie.
Do you want to live in Colony House?
Yeah.
Why are you doing this?
She chose. Your rules, Boyd, not mine.
No, you know what? It's okay.
I change my mind. I go.
I choose Colony House.
- Tabitha, just...
- What?
I'm not standing here,
knowing that my daughter
- is in that fucking house.
- Everything is gonna be okay.
- No, it's not! Fucking no.
- Okay, look.
- We're gonna fix this.
- There is nothing to fix.
Will you shut the fuck up?
Please, please, don't
do this now, right here.
My son will be up there.
I promise you she will be looked after.
All right.
Uh, everybody, the sun
will be going down soon.
So, uh, thank you for coming.
It's okay. I'll take care of him.
I'm done.
All right. Your boy, the sheriff,
crossed the line,
so just call me a car or whatever,
'cause I'm fucking done. Fuck.
I need you to understand something.
No one is trying to be cruel to you.
But you need to
understand what's going on.
Are you listening? Did
you hear what I just said?
I'm not interested.
Okay? This whole thing
lost its interest for me
the second that asshole
put his hands on me, and...
Okay, you know what?
This isn't funny anymore.
This, uh...
You hear me, guys?
It's not funny anymore!
This, uh...
Oh, God.
I... Oh, God.
Oh, God, Jesus.
Tobey?
All right, come on.
There he is.
You get these people home, Sheriff.
I'll do everything I can.
Promise me?
Yeah, Frank.
I promise.
I'm ready.
Okay.
Careful. In you go.
There's one outside.
Let's get you settled in.
This is, uh... this is Jade.
_
Uh, let's get you set up.
Are you and Daddy gonna sleep in here?
Yeah, yeah.
We're all going to be together.
Is Julie ever coming back?
Honey, she's right up the hill.
You can see her anytime you want.
- Okay.
- Okay?
Shall we have a read?
Yeah!
All right.
Last I remember, it was chapter three.
Start from the beginning.
Yeah. It has been a while.
Well, it all began one sunny morning,
as a cat lay comfortably
basking in the sun,
in a beautiful green shire.
As we always do,
let's welcome our newest family member.
Here's to Julie.
To Julie!
Thank you.
Welcome, kiddo.
Oh, we're glad to have you.
Synced & corrected by QueenMaddie
www.addic7ed.com