Previously on From...
Tabby, whatever this is, it's real,
and we are stuck.
You're telling me I'm
in a town I can't leave
and that every night monsters
come from the forest.
No!
A man protects his family, Frank!
Open your eyes and look!
Look at what you've done! Look at them!
And I wish you had the luxury
of grief, but you don't, Boyd.
These people need you.
You need to be the one to
lead these people home.
No!
Stay with me!
They're losing their leaves...
the trees.
Is it bad that they're
losing their leaves?
When things change here,
it's usually bad.
Storm wiped out half our crop.
Gonna have to get real serious about
rations with all the new people.
Last night, Elgin almost
drowned in his sleep.
He what?
Donna, I was told I can't have kids.
With all you've seen, you can't
wrap your head around a miracle?
I saw something that wasn't there.
- What?
- I saw two children,
standing in the middle of
the road, staring at me.
The night the bad things happened,
when my mother went to save the
children locked in the tower.
- ¡Mum!
- What's wrong? Julie! Julie!
What if the only way to save
Julie is to find that tower?
- Tabby...
- I have to try this, Jim. Please.
It's a Faraway tree. Here.
My mother said it would take her
to the tower, to the children.
Every time I see something
really weird, I see this symbol.
Tabitha told you she saw this
symbol down in the tunnels.
Anghkooey.
If there's answers to be found,
that's where they'll be.
Anghkooey!
Everything was fine until
you went into the forest.
I think this is gonna help me fix this.
It's not your fear that
feeds the forest, Boyd.
It's hope.
Let it go, Boyd.
If they don't die today,
they'll just die tomorrow.
No.
You don't break me.
You hear that?!
You don't fucking break me!
I'm sorry. This is the only way.
- Where am I?
- St. Anthony's Hospital.
Three days ago, a pair of
hikers found you in the woods.
You were lying unconscious
on the side of a trail.
You said "St. Anthony's
Hospital," but where is this?
You're in Camden.
Maine.
Can you tell me your name?
What?
You were found without
any identification.
Can you tell me anything
about what happened to you?
Where did you get those
cuts and bruises?
I...
- Why don't you have a seat?
- It's okay.
It's all right. No one's gonna hurt you.
Is there someone we can call?
A family member?
No.
Dr. Brody?
The police are on their way.
Thank you.
- Why...
- It's just a formality.
We all just want to make sure
you're okay, that's all.
Now that you're awake,
I'd also like to run a few tests,
if you're feeling up to it.
Would that be all right?
I'm gonna step outside for a minute,
but I'll be right down the hall.
Sit tight and rest, all right?
Hey!
Hey! Look where you're going!
What do you mean, "It's the only way"?
Get your hands off him.
I'm so sorry. I'm...
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
www.subtitulamos.tv
Shouldn't Kristi be doing that?
Kristi's got other things on her mind.
She has to look after Marielle.
Right.
How are they, by the way...
Marielle, Randall, and Julie?
They seem fine.
What?
The fact that you can look
at anything right now
and describe it as "fine"
has a bewildering charm to it.
Yeah, well, we're still here, right?
One of your own people tried
to kill you three days ago.
Half the town is still
afraid to go to sleep,
you have a food shortage
with no solution,
I'm not sure if you've noticed...
- it's getting pretty cold outside.
- Yeah, well, we got blankets.
Oh, right, yeah, I forgot
about the blankets.
Never mind. I guess we're fine then.
What do you want me to do?
Scream "fire"?
Get everybody panicked?
Maybe they aren't panicked enough.
Maybe you aren't panicked enough.
You know, when I was in that chamber,
about to smash the, music box,
that thing that was talking to me,
telling me to give up,
that hope is what the forest fed on.
That thing, whatever it was,
it sure as hell wasn't my wife.
So, what are you?
I'm afraid I can't answer
that for you, Boyd.
Stop!
No! Let me go!
We have to help her! Stop! Let me go!
Let me go!
No! Let me go!
Ethan!
We've been looking everywhere for you.
You told them, didn't you?
- Hey, I'm talking to you.
- Why'd you tell them?
We have to go find Mom!
We can't just leave her out there.
- We have to do something.
- I know.
Just, go inside, all right? Just go.
Dad!
You found him.
Good.
Hey...
Yeah, I... I'm gonna go for a walk.
Julie.
It's not your fault, Dad.
None of this is your fault.
Jim.
You know you can't do this.
I never should have let her go.
- I'm not gonna just sit around.
- Jim,
you can't be in the woods overnight.
My son just tried to run away so
that he could go look for her.
My daughter is still
refusing to talk about
whatever happened to her when she...
My kids need their mom.
What am I supposed to do?
I don't know. But it can't be this.
I'll keep a talisman in the tent.
Jim, wait. Jim!
Listen, I... Jim!
I already tried that, when I
went into the woods with Sara,
and our tent got dragged God
knows where by God knows what.
You still made it back okay.
Yeah, by the skin of my goddamn teeth.
I'm not having this conversation.
You know as well as I do that
the odds are she's already...
Don't!
Don't you fucking dare.
What's goin' on?
I'm gonna go look for my wife.
All right, wait, just hold on a second.
If you're gonna go,
there might be a safer way to do this.
Come on! You've been in there
almost an hour already!
Just give me a second.
You said that 15 minutes ago! Come on!
I can't wait any longer!
Hurry up! What are you doing in there?
It's bad enough you're
getting double rations
without you hogging the bathroom.
Back off, Nicky.
Eat shit, Clara.
Hey, is there a problem?
Yeah, there's a problem. I'm
about to piss on the floor.
Screw her.
You doing okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Baby, you really gotta eat something.
I will. I just...
My stomach just hasn't been right.
I just gotta rest.
There's two of you I
gotta worry about now.
I'll be okay.
The first couple of months
can be hard, but...
- Yeah.
- she'll be all right.
Ellis, we've got work to do.
Isn't it too soon to harvest?
We've already lost half
our crop to the storm.
I don't wanna risk losing
what little we have left,
hoping the ground doesn't freeze.
Has he slept yet?
I don't know.
We got bigger things to deal with.
Round up some bodies.
Meet me out in the field.
The day that Sara and I found
the lighthouse in the woods,
we started out at the little stone hut
where I found the talismans.
We were also in a tent that
got dragged who knows where.
But if you start out in
the hut each morning,
you're at least starting closer
to what you're trying to find,
and you've got a place to
come back to at night,
so you don't get yourself killed.
Makes sense. Thanks.
Wait. You said you and Sara
both made camp in there?
Yeah. Why?
I'm gonna go with him.
Can I talk to you outside?
Look, look, I know what
you're gonna say, okay?
But there's no way we can
let him go out there alone.
I get... I get why you're
afraid to go back...
- I am not afraid...
- Yes! Yes, you are,
and you've got a lot of
reasons to be, Boyd.
But someone's gotta make sure
that Jim comes back in one piece.
I know what it's like
to lose a parent here,
and I'm not gonna watch Julie and Ethan
lose both their parents
in the same week.
We can't play defense forever, Boyd.
What the fuck?
What the fuck is...
Jade?
They tried to show me.
I don't see it.
I can't. I can't see it. I can't see it.
They tried to show me.
What's he talking about?
No idea.
- I don't understand it.
- Did you know about this?
They're trying to show me.
I mean, I knew he was pretty obsessed
with that drawing, but this is...
insane.
I can't... I can't see it.
I can't... Fuck. I can't see it.
Yeah, I'll get that boarded up.
- No.
- I can't see it.
Help me take him back to the station.
- He can sleep it off.
- I can't see it. I can't.
- I'm gonna help you, buddy.
- No, no.
- No, no, no, no. It's all right.
- Come on... Ok.
- Let's do this.
- I gotta see... I gotta...
- No, no.
- I gotta figure this out!
Just stand up. Ready?
It's so cute.
It's amazing, like...
Look at this.
Oh, that's really cute.
Let me get one of the two of us.
- What's wrong?
- Excuse me.
Hi.
Would it be possible for me
to borrow one of your phones?
- No.
- Please.
- Will you be quick?
- Yeah.
Thank you.
Why would you do that?
Okay.
Hello?
Mom?
Tabby? Oh, God! Tabby! Where are you?
Mom, hi....
- I'm okay. We're all okay.
- Ay, mija!
Yeah.
Where have you been?
We had to go for a little while, but...
And you went where?
I just don't want you to worry, Mom.
No, Tabby, the police
are looking for you
and Jim and the kids.
Everybody's been looking!
I know. I know, Mom. I know.
- I'm so sorry.
- Ay, mi amor.
I'm gonna tell you everything
as soon as I see you.
Please! Por favor!
I just...
We have been so worried!
I just wanted to hear your voice
and for you to hear mine.
Tabby!
Mom, I love you so much,
and I miss you and...
Mi amor.
Jim and I are doing everything
we can to come back home soon.
Ay, que bueno.
Everyone says hello.
- Ay, Tabby, please, just stay on the phone.
- No, no, no.
There's a police detective.
He gave me his card.
Mom, Mom, I-I... I can't
stay here for long.
I'm sorry....
Okay, but you have to call him.
Mi amor.
You might not hear from me
for a little bit, but...
No, no, no! No, no, no!
- You have to stay here!
- I just don't want you to be afraid.
I'm okay, okay? Everything's okay.
¿Ay, pero cuándo?
- I love you, Mom.
- Tabby!
I'm so sorry, Mom. I have to go.
I love you so much, okay?
Everything's okay.
Mom, I love you. Bye.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
Why would you do that?
You seriously need to
disinfect your phone now.
When are you guys leaving?
As soon as Jim's ready.
My mom insisted on putting
together our rations.
Yeah, Moms'll do that.
Yep.
Are you sure about all this?
Mom, that's too much. We can't...
_
- Ma...
- _
- Yes.
_
It's gonna be fine!
You guys worry too much.
Are you really gonna go find Mom?
Well, I'm gonna do my best.
But I can't do that if I'm
worried about things back here.
So, no more running off, okay?
Okay.
Shake on it.
Good man.
I love you, Dad.
I love you, too.
Promise you'll be careful?
I promise.
I'll be back soon.
- Yeah.
- You got it. Okay.
You ready? We're burning daylight.
- Yeah.
- 'Kay.
Right, and remember what I
told you about those trees.
You start seeing spiderwebs,
then you know you are going
- in the right direction.
- Yeah, got it.
And whatever you do, make sure
you get back to the hut by dark.
Yeah. We're gonna be okay.
Okay? I'll see you soon.
Okay.
Dad!
You gotta come to the fields.
Come on.
Let's see what we can dig up...
No, no. Please.
What are we gonna do?
They're all fuckin' rotten.
Donna!
First things we pulled up,
it was a few rotten carrots,
beets and potatoes.
So, we pulled up some more.
They were rotten too.
Everything that survived
the storm is rotten.
Boyd, we're out of food.
How many people did you
have up here with you?
Donna!
How many people know?
Go! You go home now!
Look, I'm sorry, okay? But every
ounce of food we have left
is in those jars in your basement!
You have no right to keep
it locked away down there!
No! Those for everybody!
- There more crop coming!
- You don't know what you're talking about.
Everything else is rotten.
- This is all the food we have now!
- No!
Please go home!
Go home!
No, my house! No!
- Come on.
- What are you doing?
You're not... Look, kid, I don't
like this any more than you do,
but the shit is on the fan, all right?
- You can't! She's my friend!
- Enough.
Stop! Stop!
The kid is one thing,
- but you, I'm gonna fucking hit, all right?
- Randall, what are you doing?
I said, "Stop."
Victor, don't.
- No, no, no!
- Just stop.
No, no! Hey, hey! Stop, stop, stop!
Victor?
So, this guy's got a gun?
Are you fucking kidding me?
Is that seriously what you're
focusing on right now?
Put it down, buddy.
Victor?
Victor.
Put it down.
All right. Okay.
- Now, give me the gun, buddy.
- No.
Please, buddy.
Great.
Can I take my goat now?
Those animals are off-limits.
Those animals are the only
food that we have now.
That's right.
They provide eggs. They provide milk.
They are a resource.
And if you hadn't noticed,
we're running pretty fucking
thin on those these days.
Listen,
what happened today...
What happened today was a
setback, and I get it.
I get that we're scared. I get that...
I get that we're hungry.
But we are...
Look, we are still in this thing.
We can still win.
But whatever we do, we
have to do it carefully.
We have to make everything last.
Okay?
This place will not break us!
The only way we go home...
is together.
Okay?
So...
So, give us time to figure this out.
Give me that.
Or...
we can do this,
right here, right now.
Just give him the goat.
You people don't have any fucking idea.
You don't.
- Thank you.
- Whatever.
Hey, bud.
- You okay?
Should we take Alma back?
- Hey, could you...?
- Yeah.
Come on, Alma.
I appreciate what you're doing.
I want you to know that.
Coming out here with me... thank you.
You don't have to thank me.
Yeah, I do. I do.
Look, we're gonna do everything we can.
We're gonna be safe, and
we're gonna be smart.
What the fuck?
Hey, Jim, wait.
We should turn around.
Jim, we should head back
to the talisman hut.
It's gonna get dark soon.
These look pretty solid.
We could just hang the talisman
in one of these things,
start from here in the morning.
You're serious?
What's the difference of
sleeping in one of these things
or sleeping in the talisman hut?
Boyd said, if we saw
spiderwebs in the trees,
then we'd know we were heading
in the right direction.
He didn't say anything
about weird statues and...
Maybe Boyd's tent got
dragged past all this.
Ok.
If we're gonna spend the night here,
we should take a look around,
make sure there's no surprises.
All right.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Bless me, Father, for I have sinned.
I can't really remember when
my last confession was.
You're here now. That's what matters.
I needed to talk to someone, and
I didn't know where else to go.
I can't tell anyone who
I am, that I'm here.
They'll think I'm crazy.
I just called my mom.
That may have done more harm than good.
I don't know.
I don't know how I got here.
Nothing that I've been
through is possible.
I feel like my mind is breaking.
Whenever we reach our limits,
God will always be there
to break our fall.
No, no, no. Please...
Please don't do that.
I didn't come here to talk about God.
Why not?
Because if God is real, then
He made that horrible place.
He created all the pain and suffering.
He was the one that let my baby
fall off that changing table.
I'm sorry, Father. This was a mistake.
- Please, wait.
- I'm fine. It's okay.
What was his name?
What?
Your child, the one you lost,
What was his name?
Thomas.
That's a good name.
You have other children?
The lunchbox.
This belongs to a man named Victor.
He fixed me a snack before I left.
Before you left where?
A place where monsters
come out at night.
A place that no one can leave.
But, see,
I went through a tree that
took me to a lighthouse.
And then, a little boy
pushed me out, saying,
"This is the only way."
The only way to what?
I don't... I don't know.
I have no clue what I'm supposed
to do here or where to go.
My family is trapped
in a terrifying place,
and I don't know how
to get back to them.
What kind of snack did Victor make?
You think I'm crazy, right?
I think you're in pain,
and I'd like to help, if I can.
Humor me.
He's still such a little boy Victor.
What it must have been like for him,
growing up alone in a place like that.
_
Oh, my God. I have to go.
There's no need to rush.
No, it's okay, it's okay. I
know where to go. Thank you!
You know, this place isn't half bad
once you have the right hobby.
You really need to get some rest.
Boyd said it was okay to sleep again.
It's not that. It's...
I feel like something is watching me.
But then, I wake up and I
can never remember. I-I...
Is that her?
She looks scary.
The one thing that has
kept people hanging on
is the fact that we still
had crops coming in.
Well, they're gone.
So, now we gotta figure
out what comes next.
Right...
So, then, what do we have
left in terms of rations?
Left? We don't have anything left.
What little we had just walked
out the door in a panic!
- Then we get it back.
- And then what?
Even if we get everything
they took, which we won't,
it will still be nowhere near enough!
Then, we gotta talk about the animals.
We gotta figure out if
those animals out there
can feed everyone long
enough to plant a new crop.
The soil is poisoned!
- Everything is poisoned!
- All right, so, you wanna give up?
Look at me!
Should we just lay down and die?
Because I'm not ready to do that!
We got one resource left! One!
And we start killing those animals
without a plan, we are done!
You wanna be the one to tell Fatima her
baby's gonna starve before it's born?
Go ahead!
We plant smaller crop.
Different places.
Different soil.
Okay.
Let's say we do that.
We need those animals to buy us...
three months?
We got enough for that?
If we slaughter the cows one at a time,
they could last us at least a month.
Maybe more.
How about the goats?
We can...
Ethan.
Hey.
Mind if I join you?
Sure.
I guess you heard what we
were talking about in there.
You have to kill the
animals to feed the town.
Yeah.
Can't you find another way?
I wish I could do that.
I really do.
Those animals down there...
they're gonna save us.
They're gonna keep everybody alive
till we figure all this out.
They're gonna be heroes.
Can you make sure Alma goes first?
Why?
'Cause then she won't have
to watch her friends die.
_
Oh, for Christ's sake.
Get lost. I'm not in the mood.
Do you hear me? Get
the hell out of here.
You Deaf? I said get the...
Where did you get that?
Oh, my God.
I asked you a question.
Where did you get that?
You're...
You're his father.
You're Victor's father.
You're right about the spiderwebs.
What?
The trees with the spiderwebs.
Boyd's exact words were,
"They're fuckin' everywhere.
You can't miss 'em."
So, if we haven't seen
any spiderwebs by now,
we're probably headed
in the wrong direction.
So, what do you wanna do?
We should probably get up
to some higher ground,
see if we can't get a lay of the land.
I think it's gone.
We can't do this.
If I die out here,
I'll be leaving my kids with nothing.
There's a reason she went alone.
Because if something goes wrong...
one of us has to be there for the kids.
If she's...
She wouldn't want me out here.
We'll head home
first thing in the morning.
Fuck.
Hey.
Hi.
Want a little hair of the dog?
Oh, you been holding out.
Where'd this come from?
Father Khatri buried it in a sack
with a bloody shirt and a candy bar.
What?
It's a long story.
You ready to tell me
what's going on with you?
Not yet.
Still kinda working it out for myself.
But...
I don't think we're doing
very well here, Sheriff.
You think...
Is that a...
What the...
No. That... No!
- No, no, no!
- What the hell you doing?!
There's goddamn cows in the street!
What?!
Fuck! Wait!
Hi, babe. Hey.
We can't be out here, man.
We gotta get these
things back in the barn.
Come on, baby.
All right. Okay. Come on.
Come on, Ginger, good girl.
We'll put up a talisman
if we have to, okay?
Come on. Let's get
them back in the barn.
Come on!
Boyd?
Sheep! Sheep! Boyd! Goats! Fuck!
We have to go now before
the bad things come.
- Wait. You have to stay inside!
- What?
- You stay.
- Okay.
Lock the door. Everything be okay.
- We have to go now.
- No! Don't go!
Boyd?
Come on.
- Hey, you guys!
- This way.
Get those smaller animals
and take them back inside!
We're gonna take these
cows back to the barn.
Boyd!
Hurry up!
Come on! Come on, come on!
Pick up the pace!
Boyd!
- Boyd, look!
- Come on. Come on. Come on.
Boyd!
Fuck!
Come on. Come on, come on, come on.
Boyd?
You just keep coming!
This way. Come on. This way.
Come on!
We've gotta get inside.
Alma! Alma's outside!
What? Ethan! Hey, no!
Hello.
Go! Ethan, run! Go!
Julie!
Go!
Go, go, go!
Don't you want to play?
I have a surprise for you.
- Go.
- Come on.
Okay...
Okay. Go, go, go.
All right. Okay.
Boyd?
Boyd!
Jade, get outta there!
Get the fuck away from me.
No.
Jade!
Let's go!
Go!
Run.
Go, go. Go. Go.
Come on!
Over here!
Come on! Come on!
Go, Ethan!
Go, go, go!
Fuck!
- Victor!
- Yeah!
Get as many animals into
that barn as you can!
We can't stay here! Please! Come on.
We gotta go, okay?
Get the door!
Okay. Come on!
- Okay. Okay, okay.
- I got it!
- Go, go, go.
- Come on!
No, no, no! You go back!
No! We do together!
Push!
Come on.
Okay, babe. There we go.
There we go.
- Let's go. - Just pull her all the way in,
Tien-Chen, pull her.
Yeah. Couple more feet.
There you go. You got her?
- Yes.
- Good.
Come on.
Okay. Okay.
Right there... Fuck.
You said this place couldn't break you.
Do you remember that, Boyd?
"You don't fucking break me."
That's what you said.
No!
- No!
- No! No!
No! Let me go!
- Get off of me!
- Boyd!
- Let me go!
- No! No!
Get off me!
Get off of me!
Let her go! Let her go!
Boyd! Boyd!
Get the fuck off me!
Let her go!
Motherfuck you!
I'm gonna fucking kill you!
- Boyd!
- Get these fucking things off me!
- Kill me!
But you leave her alone!
We're not gonna kill you, Boyd.
That would be no fun.
You think this place can't break you?
Let's see.
No. No, no, no, no, no!
Don't! What the fuck?!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
No, no! Hey, hey, hey! Look at me!
- Boyd!
- I know, I know, I know!
Look at me!
Can... can you say... look! Look!
Open your eyes! Look at me!
What?
Okay. Say... say it again!
I know! I know. Look! Come on.
Please don't, don't.
Don't!
Okay! Okay! No! Keep looking at me.
I'm sorry. You're so strong!
You're so strong.
Just...
No, no, no, no, no, no! I know,
I know, I know, I know, I know.
I know! I know! No, God!
I know! Look! Look at me.
No, no, no. Look at me. Look at me.
Look. Keep your eyes on me.
www.subtitulamos.tv