Previously on From...
Are you looking for these?
Take them. We get to
keep Randall, though.
We're gonna need some fresh towels!
- You're gonna hurt yourself.
- You fucking left me!
Ellis, he's so happy.
I can't tell him how scared I am.
I'm trying to be patient,
- but I need...
- You can't help!
I don't understand.
This.
- It's all I can keep down!
- What?
I think there's something
wrong with the baby.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing for Christopher.
- Who was Christopher?
- He was our friend.
But then Christopher
started seeing the symbol,
and then everyone died.
Jasper's the one who can
tell us why it happened.
Easier to tell myself they were dead.
All that time, my little boy was here.
What kind of man gives up on his family?
Victor.
I didn't know how to get home.
What the hell happened last night?
- Boyd.
- Tabitha's back.
What?
Boyd said you went through a tree?
They're called Farway trees.
Can you get back there without the tree?
- I don't know. I don't know.
- What about the bottles?
- Was there anything special about them?
- I took a few of 'em down.
There were slips of paper inside
with numbers written on them.
When you were out there,
did you contact anyone?
You don't understand, they
wouldn't have believed me.
You had an opportunity that none
of us have ever had before,
and you blew it.
I went out and I came back.
And I came back with nothing.
We thought you were dead.
Your children thought you were dead.
You owe it to your kids to be here now.
What are you doing?
I had a nightmare.
You wanna talk about it?
No.
Come back to bed.
I should've done more.
When I was out there, I
should've done more.
You did the best you could.
How do you know that?
What?
You keep saying stuff like that.
How do you know?
How do you have any idea
what I could've done?
- I'm just...
- You keep saying stuff like that,
just that is not true,
just so I feel better.
I don't understand.
Would you rather I
just picked you apart?
Make you feel like shit?
I'm not gonna do that.
I just want you to be honest.
No.
What you want
is for me to read your mind,
so I can say to you
whatever you wanna hear
at any given time.
You want me to be the bad guy?
Fine!
But I was the one who stayed here,
holding our kids together,
while you ran off
- to try to deal with whatever...
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
it was you were doing!
You make it sound like I
went on a fucking vacation.
I came to you. I asked for
your fucking permission.
I was just trying to save our daughter.
Did it ever occur to you that maybe
we could've done things together?
No! Because you wanted
to do it on your own!
You want to do everything on your own!
- That's why you...
- That's why what?
- Nothing.
- Noth... That's why what?
- I'm going back to bed.
Stop being a fucking coward and tell me!
That's why you wanted a divorce,
because it'd be easier
for you to cut and run,
to deal with Thomas's death on your own,
instead of trying to put
our family back together!
Oh, yeah and you were the
knight in shining armor, right?
Everything you did, every
choice you made was perfect!
- I never said that.
- You think getting the divorce
was gonna let me deal with it on my own?
- I was already on my fucking own!
- Oh, that's so not true.
You got to throw
yourself into your work!
You were not there when Julie
and Ethan woke up crying.
You didn't see them
sitting in Thomas's room,
just staring at his toys...
- No.
- And you're upset.
You're upset
because you had to take care of your
children the few days that I was gone?
I took care of my fucking
kids for a year,
- while you were doing I don't know
fucking what. - No! God damn it! No!
- Where are you going?
- Downstairs!
www.subtitulamos.tv
Hey.
You slept late.
Where's Dad?
He went to the lake with some
people to get the rest of the food.
He left?
Yeah. He's coming back tomorrow.
Go tell Ethan I'm making breakfast.
So we're just taking day
trips to the lake now?
Honey, the people need the food.
Right.
And it had nothing to do with
that screaming match last night?
I'm sorry you heard that.
I'm pretty sure people
in Colony House heard.
- Listen, Julie...
- No.
I get it. I've heard this
speech plenty of times.
I'm just glad some things are
finally getting back to normal.
I'll get Ethan.
So you're saying this could
be some kind of code?
Yeah, or an algorithm, or... who knows?
Look, the fact is, Tabitha got
pushed out of a lighthouse
and somehow ended up near a
hiking trail in Camden, Maine.
I don't think I'm being
controversial when I say,
by all known metrics, that's impossible.
- Okay.
- Unless... Unless...
she experienced some kind of...
quantum event.
Right? Or wormhole, or any
number of theoretical events
that would allow her to get from
the lighthouse in the woods
to Camden, Maine.
Or maybe...
Maybe the lighthouse in the
woods occupies the same space
as Camden, Maine.
Maybe it wasn't a wormhole so
much as a dimensional rift!
- Jade. - I can understand an
awful lot of people get confused,
but the truth is a wormhole is a
shortcut through space and time.
- Whereas a dimensional rift...
- Jade, stop!
Sorry. What?
I thought you said you had
something exciting to show me.
Yeah.
All right, okay, okay, listen, listen.
I understand why you might be skeptical.
I am too.
Something tells me that
this has to mean something.
The bottle tree was important
to Miranda, right?
And according to Tabitha,
she's the only one
who had a connection to this
place long before she arrived.
Did you look at the bottles
from the other tree?
What other tree? The one in Maine?
- No. How could I...?
- No, the one...
Sara and I found one of these trees
when we went out into
the woods together.
It wasn't a portal tree,
but it still had bottles
hanging from it,
messages inside. I pulled
one down, it said...
1864.
Eighteen.
Eighteen six...
I saw it.
"1864."
Where's the second tree?
Hey.
Sorry.
I was looking for you and
I just figured I'd wait.
Okay.
I haven't seen one of
these in a long time.
Yeah. That belonged to Mrs. Davis.
Is that right?
What was Mrs. Davis doing
with one of these?
She bought it for her son,
he was very sick,
and he saw the car in
the back of a magazine.
And so, she drove
far away to buy one from the only store
that still sold them.
She...
She said her son didn't have very long,
and she knew that the
car would make him...
smile.
She saw the tree before she got home.
And she died a long time ago.
I guess her son is dead too.
I was thinking maybe
you could show me around today.
There's something I have to do.
It's very important.
Mind if I tag along?
No, I don't think that's a good idea.
Right.
Well, I'll...
- I'll just get out of your way.
- It's...
It's... very dangerous,
what I have to do, and I...
I don't want you to get hurt.
But you could walk with me
for a bit, if you want.
All right. I'd like that.
Okay.
I finished cleaning out the ambulance.
Here's the last of it.
Awesome. Thanks.
Oh, this stuff is gonna be a godsend.
I'm gonna bring this downstairs.
Oh, I can give you a hand.
You've done plenty, really.
You should go home,
get some rest.
Thank you.
Coming or going?
Oh, I... going.
You okay?
Yeah. You know, I...
I'm good.
Yeah.
- Kenny...
- I'm good.
I'm good, really.
I don't wanna talk about it right now.
Okay.
- Yeah.
Boyd.
Shouldn't you be in bed?
I don't think you're one to
talk about taking it easy.
Well...
He's doing better.
Yeah.
Yeah. I was...
I was just...
Hey, that ambulance
came in fully stocked.
There was a portable ultrasound onboard.
- Really?
- Yeah.
When you see Fatima,
tell her to come on by.
She can take a look
at her little nugget.
I'll do that.
Hey, look, don't mention
that I came by, okay?
- Yeah, of course.
- Right.
That's really good news, the ultrasound.
Yeah.
Say something.
We have to go to Kristi.
No.
I can't do that.
There's gotta be some sort
of medical explanation.
How can there be?
Look, I don't...
I don't want everyone looking at me
the way that you're
looking at me right now.
Like you're afraid of me.
No, no, I am not afraid of you.
Okay?
And whatever is happening is not
your fault, okay? I just...
I just wanna help you.
Maybe it'll just go away, you know?
Maybe it'll just go away on its own.
- And maybe...
- Baby...
Maybe it'll just stop.
Who is it?
It's Dad.
I got some good news.
Just a second. Just a second.
Hey.
Hey, look at me.
I am just as scared as you.
Okay?
But we cannot do this alone.
If it's a bad time...
No, it's fine.
Okay.
Hey. What's...
What's going on?
Come in.
Donna?
I heard about what happened.
I'm so sorry.
Were you two close?
He was a pain in my ass
for almost two years.
He had some good moments, though.
Would have loved this;
me hauling these fucking
stones across town.
Only thing he would've liked better,
is if I left him to rot,
so he could ruin everyone's
breakfast every morning.
I was there when he went through.
He was just trying to help, you know?
I'm sure he had some shitty
remark on his way out.
You doing okay?
Yeah, yeah.
That meeting yesterday
couldn't have been too easy.
Well, I just...
I just feel that...
everyone expects me to have
all the answers, you know?
I feel like I let them down.
I feel like I let my family down.
Let them down?
Tabitha, your children
thought you were dead.
They don't need answers from you.
They just needed you back.
Yeah.
What if the people from
the meeting were right?
What if I wasted
the only opportunity we're gonna get?
You see Dale down there?
You went through that same tree.
That could have been you down there.
I know.
Don't try to be a hero.
Go spend time with your kids
because you're lucky to be here still.
Don't take that for granted.
I'm done.
Hey.
I'm sorry about your friend.
- Well, back to work.
- Yeah.
You...
tell those kids of yours I said hello.
I will.
So you wanna go down into the tunnels,
where these things live?
I don't want to. I have to.
Because there's something down there
that is going to help people?
It's going to save them.
It'll save you too.
We're here.
You should go now.
Do you remember the way back?
I'm not going back. I'm...
- coming with you.
- No, that's not a good idea.
I just got you back.
I'm not losing you again.
If you're gonna do this,
we're doing it together.
Okay.
What are those for?
So we don't get lost.
Follow close.
Hey, and be really, really quiet.
I mean, we've seen things
here that don't make sense.
And...
these cravings,
maybe it's just...
I mean, maybe it's just the effect
that this place has on pregnancy,
so it doesn't have to mean that there's
something wrong with the baby, right?
Right.
Kristi has an ultrasound machine.
Wait. What?
It was on the ambulance
that came into town.
That's what I came to tell you.
No.
I-I don't... I don't...
I don't wanna.
Could you give us a second?
Oh, yeah, of course.
Yeah.
Fatima...
- Ellis, I don't want to see it.
- No, we can't...
We cannot just hope
- that this gets better, okay?
- I know.
Okay. We are in the dark.
I know. We'll do it tomorrow.
We'll go tomorrow.
Fatima, Fatima...
- I just want it to be okay.
- I know.
It's okay.
- I just want it to be okay.
- I know, baby.
- I'm sorry.
- Okay.
I know.
Good, you're awake.
The fuck do you want?
We need to change your bandages.
It's fine.
I need to make sure
there's no infection.
That's not something you want, not here.
Fine. I'll fuckin' change 'em.
I need you to sit up.
Please. Come on.
Yeah. Okay, yeah.
May I?
Yeah.
Well?
There's no sign of infection.
And the stitches are holding well.
There's gonna be a lot of
bruising, a lot of discomfort.
I wanna see it.
Give me a minute?
Yeah, take your time.
Hey.
What are you doing?
You're not gonna tell
my parents, are you?
If you get caught, I was never here.
- Deal.
- Okay.
You want some?
- Don't push it.
- All right.
Hey, I was looking for the screwdriver.
My mom always kept a junk
drawer in the kitchen.
Yeah. My dad gets fidgety
when he's nervous,
so he probably just moved stuff around.
- Okay.
- God, no.
- No.
- I'm sorry.
With my mom being gone, he
probably didn't even realize.
No, it's fine. It's just a junk drawer.
I'm sorry.
It's not a big deal, seriously.
I'm gonna go check the dining room.
You just keep that under wraps.
'Kay?
Okay.
Oh God.
How much further?
This way.
No, he...
He should be here.
This is where I saw him.
This whole chamber was full.
- Now it's not.
- Maybe we took a wrong turn.
No.
Jasper, he was sitting right here.
There was a clock
and a wheelchair.
And the bad things, they were sleeping.
Hey, maybe we should go back.
- You can get your bearings.
- I know where I am.
We need to go deeper.
I'm not sure that's a good idea.
- We can't leave without Jasper.
- Victor.
It's important.
We'll be okay.
This way.
She's coming.
She just...
She just needs a minute.
Thanks.
Hey, smile.
What?
Me and Julie found this in the basement.
I figured we should put together a
little Colony House photo album.
Doesn't have to all be scary and bad.
Okay.
I'm gonna put a collage on the wall,
if you wanna check it out later.
You ready?
I don't wanna say anything...
to Kristi,
not until we have to.
Okay.
You're coming, right?
Whatever you guys need.
All right.
Great.
And then there were two.
Oh, for fuck's sake!
It's ironic, no?
A drunk looking for answers in
a tree filled with bottles.
Why are you wiping that glass?
A man does what a man does.
So, you really think this
is gonna tell you anything?
I think this place has a design.
I don't think anything's
here by accident.
Maybe that's your problem.
And what, dead Tom, does that mean?
Well...
nature has a design, Jade,
and that is not nature.
It's just something somebody put there.
Sure, it might mean something, yeah.
Maybe it's something someone made
because they thought it meant something.
Maybe it's someone like you..
Just looking for answers,
trying to figure things out.
Grasping at straws.
And here you are, standing,
looking at this bottle tree,
puzzling over it
like it's a part of
the original design.
No.
Miranda had visions of this place.
She had visions of these trees.
You don't have visions
about things that don't mean anything.
What about the things you see?
The Civil War soldiers.
The guy crushed by the rock
- in the root cellar.
- No, no, no.
Listen, those were different. Okay?
Those were completely different.
How so, Jade?
Fine! All right, fine!
Maybe it's garbage. Maybe this
is a giant waste of time.
Are you gonna help me
bring these down or what?
I gotta finish this first.
For fuck's sake...
Jade. You mad?
I am a little bit annoyed, yeah.
You should work on that.
Because the Jade that built a
multi-million-dollar company
when everyone said he shouldn't,
that guy had thicker skin.
Yeah.
You really wanna beat this place?
Maybe you should sober up
and give that guy a call.
There's a nicer way to
make your point, you know!
Hey, buddy.
What ya got there?
It's Tian Chen's.
Did you learn to read
Chinese while I was gone?
No.
Where's your sister?
She went for a walk.
Do you think Tian-Chen's
with her husband now?
I hope so.
Do you think they were happy
when they got married?
Honey...
I'm so sorry you heard
us fight last night.
I'm so sorry.
We're just trying to do our best...
for all of us.
I liked it better when
we first got here.
Everyone was so scared, there
was no time to be angry.
I wish it could be like that again.
What's Jade doing at the bar?
That's what you guys were
fighting about, right?
Jade...
he's trying to figure out a puzzle.
What kind of puzzle?
Is someone upstairs?
No.
Are you sure?
What's wrong?
Wait.
- Anghkooey.
- Oh my God.
- Why are you here?
- Anghkooey.
- No, no, no, no, no.
- Oh my God.
- Anghkooey.
- I tried to help you.
I tried to help you. Leave us alone.
- Anghkooey.
- Oh, my God.
- No, no, no, no, no.
- Anghkooey.
- Mom?
Mom?! Anghkooey!
- Mom!
- What?
Are you okay?
What? We're okay.
It's okay, it's okay. It's okay.
Oh my God.
- We're okay. It's okay.
- Was it the children?
Yes.
- Can we go outside?
- Yes. Let's go. Let's go.
It's really nice of you
to do this for him.
Would've hated it.
"Great. A pile a rocks? That all I get?"
Well...
it's not just rocks.
It's dignity.
Everyone deserves that.
Yes, they do.
You don't have to be here, honey.
You've already been
through enough of this.
Actually, I was...
kinda wondering if you maybe had
some extra space up at Colony House.
For me.
She was the only thing that ever
made that house feel like a home.
It was meant for a family.
She'd want them to have it.
We always have room for you.
You're not still throwing those sex
parties up there, are you? 'Cause I...
Oh, just go pack your stuff
before I change my mind.
Yes, ma'am.
There we go.
Can we come in?
I'm a little busy.
Well, I told Ethan we can
help you with your puzzle.
Sure. Yeah.
You like puzzles, buddy?
Yeah.
Well, great, 'cause this one just
got a whole lot more interesting.
How?
Turns out there is a second bottle tree.
There's two of them?
Not only that, but the messages
in the bottles, the numbers,
they're all the same.
I mean, the placement's
obviously different,
and in the second tree, they're
written out in cursive.
But the actual numbers,
you line them up side by side;
they are exactly the same.
Not to mention some of them
repeat, over and over again.
What does that mean?
I have no idea.
But I am increasingly optimistic
that, somewhere in here,
somewhere in these dates,
in these numbers, is a key
to something that we need to understand.
You wanna help me find it?
Okay.
You need to apply this every
time you change the bandages.
I heard you the first time.
That gets infected,
- you're gonna be in a world of...
- I said I heard you.
Okay.
You're all set, then.
Why are you pretending you're okay?
If you're talking about
Nicky, that was...
No, you know what I'm talking about.
Just make sure you change the bandages.
You can pretend all you want,
but you were there,
same as me.
What if it's not over?
Whatever happened to us, it wasn't...
What?
It wasn't real?
What the fuck is "real" anymore?
It's gotta be easy for you in a
place like this, though, huh?
Going to sleep next to
somebody every night.
You get to pretend that you're okay.
Yeah, well, it's not like
that out on the bus.
I don't get to pretend.
It's fucking...
terrifying.
So, then, don't go back to the bus.
We got room.
Go get your stuff.
You serious?
Yeah.
No one here has to be alone.
I'll talk to Kristi.
Okay.
How many of those little
green men do you have?
We'll be fine.
- Careful.
- All right.
Victor, I think we should turn around.
It won't be much further.
You don't know that.
If we get lost down here...
We won't get lost.
- Careful.
- Hey, hey, look.
- We can come back.
- No.
- Figure out a plan.
- No!
Victor, please...
- Wait, wait.
- What?
Look, look, look.
We have to go through.
No, Victor.
No. Wait, wait.
Okay.
Let's go. Let's go.
Oh, God.
This is... it's your mother's.
We have to go.
You know, Victor, if you
keep coming down here,
one of these days, we'll make you stay.
Go!
Go, go, go!
Go! Come on!
You movin' out?
Yeah.
Found a sweet little condo up the road.
Yeah?
Yeah. Ocean views. Indoor gym.
Sounds nice.
Yeah.
Where are you really going?
Marielle said I could
stay at the clinic.
How's she doing?
She's acting like nothing ever happened.
How are you doing?
Get stoned a lot.
It helps.
You got anything on you now?
Okay.
Come inside.
Careful.
Be careful. Come on.
Sit here.
Okay.
That thing, its voice...
It's okay. We're safe now.
Why did they have this?
It's your mother's.
I don't know. They like to take things.
Why?
I don't know. They just do.
What is this place?
It's...
just somewhere...
somewhere I come when it
gets too loud sometimes.
I used to hide here...
before the people came.
At night? You would hide in here?
Because you were alone.
My God.
- It's okay.
- My God.
No, everything is okay now.
Look, we found Jasper.
That means that we can save people.
How?
He knows things.
Yeah.
I heard him tell Christopher a
story about this place once,
and we have to make him tell it again.
But Victor...
Victor...
that's a toy.
We'll make him tell it again.
You'll see.
Okay. Let's lift this up.
- I got the gel.
- Oh, great. Thank you.
All right, so, it's just
gonna be a bit cold.
Now, keep in mind,
it's still early days,
so it's not gonna look like much yet.
It'll be about the size of an acorn,
and if we're lucky, we might
see the arms and legs.
So, just, keep your
expectations in check, okay?
Okay.
Ready?
Okay, so, there's your uterus.
What's going on?
I...
I don't see anything.
What do you mean?
You're not pregnant.
No.
No, that's impossible.
I need you to keep looking.
- Fatima...
- You barely looked!
Just keep looking!
- Sweetie, I'm so sorry...
- I don't need you to be sorry!
- I need you to look again.
- Hey, it's okay.
- It's not okay!
- It's okay, just...
Okay, we'll take a look together, okay?
- It's okay.
- All right.
So right here is where the
baby's supposed to be.
But there's nothing there.
No, I...
There's something inside of me.
I need you to find it.
Fatima...
there's nowhere else to look.
We need to tell them.
Tell us what?
Help me, Elgin.
I can save you.
I can save all of you.
I can help you go back home.
Hey.
Are you all right?
You look weird.
I'm fine.
I like the collage.
The fact that some of
the numbers repeat,
that means there's a pattern somewhere.
The 2 on this one's backwards.
Same thing with the number seven,
but they're only backwards sometimes.
- Why?
- I don't know.
That's why we have to
figure out the pattern.
If we can figure out the pattern,
then we can figure out the shape.
Get cracking.
Look...
whatever those kids are,
they're not gonna hurt you.
How do you know that?
They want your help, right?
I don't know.
Maybe.
I'm basing that on
something a dead woman saw
in a vision 40 years ago, so...
I don't know.
What is this?
Some wards scattered
around the settlement.
I'm guessing they're protective.
They don't really seem...
What's wrong?
Three red stones.
What?
Did you see three red stones,
big ones, in a circle?
How did you...?
No.
No, no.
When I was a little girl,
I would have the same nightmare
over and over again.
It wasn't just Miranda.
I saw this place too...
but I just didn't know it.
www.subtitulamos.tv