Synced & corrected by QueenMaddie
www.addic7ed.com
Previously on From...
If these voices are real,
if something here is
communicating with you,
then that means you're
connected to this place
in a way that no one else here is.
But we need proof.
What is this?
They said they watched
you bury the bag
and that this is proof
that they're real.
Do you know what that means?
Can I have my pillow back?
I just want to take a nap
and it's sort of like a security
blanket for me, you know?
Yeah, I totally get it. I'm sorry again.
You know, it's kinda funny.
I have a shirt just like that.
Oh, I know. I got this
out of your suitcase.
What's wrong?
I think maybe I-I made a mistake.
I knew all about the divorce
and how this whole trip
was just one last hurrah
before you sat us
down to break the news.
Thomas is dead! You have two other kids!
Why aren't we enough for you?
What is that?
A Farway Tree.
Watch.
How does it do that?
I don't know. But guess what.
- What?
- It works for people too.
Really?
Problem is, you never
know where you'll end up.
There's no wire in here.
- What?
- In the cord. And the plug?
Look. None of it makes any sense.
Mom!
Everything about this is impossible,
but we can find out
where those wires go.
There was this weird fucking
symbol right on the ceiling!
What are you looking for? Hmm?
I have this crazy idea that
might actually work, and...
And if it does,
I might be able to find a
way to get these people home.
They're so beautiful.
I'm so glad you like them.
When can I come inside?
What? Not acceptable. No way.
Oh, let's not make a big deal.
It's a party, you guys, like...
- Okay, pick one.
- Um, this one.
I don't know, it just seems kinda weird
to be celebrating the day
that you got stuck here.
You're looking at this the wrong way.
It's about celebrating survival.
It reminds everybody that it's possible.
Besides, it's nice having a
little party once in a while.
Okay, what are you looking for?
I am not looking. I am digging.
Aha! Here it is.
It's my secret stash.
Trudy loves this sweater.
It's the one thing I own that I
don't let her get her hands on.
Besides, it is Ellis' favorite.
What?
Nothing. Uh...
You just... you make this
place seem almost normal.
You're really special.
Don't be silly.
We're all really special.
Even Trudy.
That's something a really
special person would say.
There's my girls.
Uh, anybody up for a little pregame?
Baby, the party hasn't even started yet.
I know! I know! That's
why they call it pregame.
What?
Nothing.
Just... go easy, okay?
Yeah, I know. I know. I know.
Uh, Julie?
- How 'bout you?
- Uh... I'm good, thanks.
Okay.
Okay, whatever. You guys suck.
Victor? Victor, where you at, man?
Let's get this party started!
Is he okay?
Nights like this are just
a little tough for him.
As much as you celebrate
the people who make it,
you also remember the ones who didn't.
Here, you should wear this.
It'll look really cute.
Okay, come on, man.
I mean, you of all people
should be hammered today.
I mean, how many years
have you been here for?
Please leave me alone.
- Oh...
- Ellis!
Ellis!
You want a shot?
Okay.
Donna, there's no more peaches.
I know. We're, uh...
We're all out.
They're gone?
I thought I had a few more cans
stashed away in the basement,
but, uh...
I've been putting some
other things aside for you.
Some fruit cocktail. Some cranberries...
The peaches are gone.
All these years, that's...
That's the one thing
that's never changed,
and now they're gone.
I'm sorry, Victor.
Yeah.
Kevin, come on! It'll be dark soon.
Coming.
"There was so much joy on the faces"
"of all the new wondrous
friends she had made,"
"so much magic in all the
marvelous places she had been."
"Yet the Cromenockle had a feeling
"there was still more yet to come,
"and that her adventures
in this strange new world
truly had just only begun."
Jade?
I say you could come in?
My mom wants us to get dinner started.
Come on.
- What are you doing?
- What the hell, man?
- I was reading this!
- There's no other paper here!
That doesn't mean start
drawing in my fucking book.
You want me to write on your walls?
Like a psychopath?!
What are you doing out here?
I, uh, think there's some
things we need to talk about.
In private.
All right, come by in the morning.
No. I think we should do this now.
It's important.
I guess we're having a sleepover then.
Come on in.
Looks like you're going somewhere.
Yeah. I was gonna come by and
talk to you about all this.
Well, we have more to
talk about than I thought.
He's completely passed out.
Well, pretty sure
you violated about a
dozen child labor laws
by having him dig in
the basement all day.
No, he was having fun.
He just wanted to help.
I get so nervous every
time I take my eyes off him.
Yeah. Yeah, me too.
But, look, windows are nailed shut.
The doors are locked.
He couldn't let one of
those things in if he tried.
Yeah, yeah.
Fuck! And then I think
about Julie up in that house.
Donna, the lady who runs
the place, she might be a...
But she's definitely not stupid.
Yeah.
How's it going?
Well...
provided I can convince the sheriff
to let me use all of
their building materials,
not to mention drain every
single battery they've got,
and get Donna to allow us to build
on the high ground at Colony House,
should be just promising enough
for everyone to hate me when it fails.
Oh, come on, don't say that.
You got a signal.
No, come on. I got static.
That's a far cry from a signal.
Well, but it's something.
Yeah.
Hey. Hey.
It matters.
And look, look on the bright side,
at least we've got our hole in
the basement to fall back on.
Or in.
Or in. I'm gonna head back down.
Best get to it.
Oh, shit.
Hey, watch where
you're going, man. Fuck.
Hey, hey, hey. Hey! Hold on.
- Hey.
- Maybe slow down a little bit.
Hey, I'm... I'm fine. I'm fine.
It's a party, right?
Don't worry.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, I think so.
He said not to worry,
so I'm going to worry.
All right, everybody settle down now!
- Everybody!
- We should go.
Yeah, yeah, yes.
Hey, shut your fucking mouths!
All right.
We are here tonight
to celebrate a very special anniversary.
Yeah.
One year ago today...
Our dear sweet Fatima
came into our lives.
Some of you were here then,
many of you arrived since.
But all of you have come to know her
and to love her,
for her kindness, for her strength,
for her wisdom...
And for her weed!
The green thumb is
definitely a big plus.
Our greenhouse never smelled so good.
But, uh, seriously,
the truth is...
you've made this big old drafty box
feel a little bit more like home.
Happy anniversary, sweet pea.
Donna...
Thank you.
This is so beautiful.
May it catch all the bad dreams...
And let only the sweet ones reach you.
- Come here.
- Thank you.
Oh. We are so lucky to have you.
So lucky to have...
All right with the mushy.
All right, everybody,
you all know the protocol.
Drink, smoke, have fun,
keep an eye on each other.
- Cheers!
- Cheers.
Cheers, baby.
Happy anniversary, gorgeous.
Thank you.
Look at what she got me.
She made this herself.
Aw!
So, that's the plan. Yup.
Find a way outta here once and for all
before it all comes
crashing down around us.
Your turn.
I buried this bag the day I arrived.
Open it.
Holding out on me?
This yours?
I'm not talking about the shirt.
I'm talking about the blood.
There's another item in the bag.
I mean, what... what is it?
What the fuck is going on?
We've never really discussed
who we used to be...
before we came here.
There was this young
boy in my congregation.
He was quiet, sensitive.
He used to get so excited
when his mother let him put
a dollar in the collection plate.
One day, after mass,
I found him lingering
outside the rectory
and it was unusual.
You know, he wasn't
really the type of kid
to stray too far from his parents.
They were very, um...
strict...
rigid.
And I get it. Parents,
they worry about their kids,
and sometimes you have...
I'm sorry. Do you mind?
Anyway, the point is...
the boy was upset.
He asked if he could stay a while.
But I had to prepare for evening mass
and I didn't want the parents to worry.
So I, uh...
I went to my drawer and
I pulled out a candy bar.
I, uh... I always keep a stash
for the neighborhood kids.
I could see he didn't want to go.
But I handed it to him
and I sent him on his way.
Later that evening, I,
uh... I went by the house.
It was a bit unorthodox.
You know, I'm not really in
the habit of making house calls,
but something was
nagging me and I just...
As I walked up the driveway,
the mother, she came running out,
hysterical...
inconsolable.
She was...
And I could smell the alcohol
the moment I stepped through the door.
The father was just...
standing there with this panicked,
dumbfounded look on his face.
"Get up! Get up!" he said.
I walked over and I stepped
in the room, and there he was.
This sweet, innocent boy,
just laying there, broken.
His neck was bulging
in a way... It was...
And I could see, in his pocket...
the candy bar.
"He'll be fine."
That's what the father
said. "He'll be fine."
It was the way he said it.
Sounded indignant.
The next thing I knew,
I was on top of him,
smashing his face as hard as I could.
I couldn't stop.
I just kept hitting
him over and over again.
I couldn't stop.
Even when I felt the bones
in my hand start to break,
I couldn't stop.
I was the one who was
supposed to listen.
I was the one who was supposed
to defend the defenseless.
That sweet little boy came
to me begging for help,
and all I could do was
give him a candy bar.
A fucking candy bar!
The next thing I remember,
I was standing on a bridge,
holding that bottle in my hand.
And it was the first time in my life
that I heard the voice of God.
He told me to get back in the car,
that there was another
path for me to follow.
So I did.
I got back in the car and I drove,
and two hours later, I was here.
Why are you telling me all this now?
Because I have Sara tied up
in the basement of the church.
Look, I've always known that
there's a reason we're here,
that there's a path
we're meant to follow,
and I know it may seem...
Tell me you're joking.
- Boyd...
- Tell me you are motherfucking joking!
Are you gonna shoot me?
I might fucking shoot you, yeah!
You told me that Frank broke the rules.
Frank had to go in the box!
And now you just... That girl...
That girl may be the key
to unlocking all this.
That girl...
may be the way we all go home.
Keep talking.
Okay.
Jasmine.
Jasmine!
What's wrong?
I only came to say goodbye.
What? Wait, wait, wait.
I don't understand.
Just please talk to me.
Why won't you let me in?
You know why. I can't.
Please, just stay and talk with me.
You said you liked me.
I do!
I can't keep coming here,
knowing I'll see you but
never get to feel you,
knowing you're afraid of me,
that you're disgusted by me.
No. It...
You always tell me how
lonely you are in there.
You have no idea how
lonely it is out here.
It wasn't my choice to be this way.
Goodbye, Kevin.
Wait, wait.
You know, there's a
party going on downstairs.
Everyone's having a really good time.
But you are the only one
that I want to be with.
You are the only one
that I can really talk to.
You promise it'll just be
you? No one else can get in?
Not once we shut the window, I promise.
Okay.
And now, the question is...
How many dimensions are there?
Bosonic string theorists
believe there are 26 dimensions,
but superstring theorists
say there's only 10.
And is that what this place is?
Another dimension?
Oh, no, no.
This is a pocket universe.
Oh, my God.
For Christ's sake, man, enough.
It's not a pocket universe;
it's not whatever the
fuck you think it is,
and nobody gives a fuck.
So why don't you shut the fuck up, man?
Yeah, okay, have another drink.
All right, calm down.
Jesus!
- Hey!
- What are you gonna do about it? Huh?
- Hey! All right, okay.
- What are you gonna do?
Take him upstairs before he
starts shooting up the place.
- No, no, no, no!
- Hey, hey, hey! That's enough.
That's enough! Now, ease up!
You okay?
Hey, you okay?
Yeah, I'm sorry. I, um...
I'm just gonna go upstairs and lay down.
Okay. I'll come with you.
Nah, it's fine. It's
fine. Hey, I'm just, uh...
It's your night.
Just stay.
Goddamn animal.
Like mother, like son.
You stay the fuck outta my sight.
Now, close the window, quick.
See? Just the two of us.
Just the two of us.
My handsome boy.
Your hands are so warm.
Did you think they would be cold?
Kiss me.
What?
Dinner's ready.
I'm not hungry.
You've been staring at that book
for a day and a half,
maybe you should...
- Just fuck off. Just fuck off.
- You know what, Jade?
Okay! Okay! Okay! Okay!
I'm coming! Jesus!
Uh, I wouldn't take
too long if I were you.
You know, you should really
work on your party face.
What are you doing, sitting
here all by yourself?
You don't have to.
I know you don't like me.
That's not true.
I just...
It's such a nice party.
You'll get one too.
No.
I don't think I will.
Take off your shirt.
What?
I'm not gonna lie. You
drive me crazy sometimes.
But we're in this together.
You're not alone.
Really?
Think of it as an early
gift for your anniversary.
You know what?
Much as I hate to admit,
it looks better on you.
That's wildly untrue.
But thank you.
I'm gonna find something
to give you, too.
Excuse me.
That was nice of you.
Everybody needs a little
pick-me-up sometimes.
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
Uh, that girl that you...
That you kissed before?
Who? Stacey? Yeah, she's great.
Yeah, I'm just... I thought
you and Ellis were... together.
Oh. Oh, God, yeah. Yeah, no.
Ellis, he's... he's my person.
That thing with Stacey, that's
just, you know, fooling around.
Oh, okay.
Do you think...
Could I kiss you?
Oh, um, Julie...
No. I was... I was just
kidding. I didn't mean...
- No, sweetie...
- No, you know what? Just forget it.
So, this girl tells you she's
hearing voices and you just...
Look, I was skeptical.
Just like you, okay?
But then...
she showed me this.
Look at that.
That's the logo...
I know what it is.
That was almost three years ago.
Sara and Nathan have been
here, what? Four, five months?
All right, so you told
someone, someone told Sara...
I never told a soul.
Boyd, there was no possible
way she could have known.
Something was watching me that day,
the same thing that told Sara...
And you think this thing
is trying to help us?
By killing an old man and a child?
Whatever it is, it's a part
of the fabric of this place.
Okay? Whatever connection Sara has
makes her valuable in ways we
may not even understand yet.
Okay, now if you want to put
her in the box, that's fine.
I'm not gonna stop you.
But if you're serious
about finding answers...
the fact that you're going on
this journey at the same time
that this connection is revealed,
that's not just a coincidence.
That's providence.
So, what are you suggesting?
That we go with you, Sara and I. Okay?
We use this connection to our advantage.
So, a priest, a sheriff,
and a murdering psycho walk into a bar.
Yeah, something like that, yeah.
What?
If we go any deeper, we're
gonna need a taller ladder.
Well, we'll go as deep as we have to.
Here, come here.
Let me take a look at that.
I'm fine, really.
"Fine" is not a word I would use
to describe any of us at this point.
- Ow!
- That's it. Yeah.
- Oof!
- Little bit harder?
Why don't you take a break?
Go sit with Ethan for a bit.
I'll take over here.
Are you stuck on your antenna?
- Yeah. Pretty much.
- Ow. Go slow, please.
Oh, my God.
How's that?
It's amazing.
Can I come in?
I'd rather you didn't.
Please?
This is the only place in
this house I can be alone.
Well, sort of.
- You look sad.
- Can I just come in?
I'm having a really bad night.
Are you going somewhere? It
looks like you're packing.
No, I'm just...
No. It's hard to explain.
Why did you dig those graves?
I don't want to talk about that.
Are these from all the cars
that have come into town?
Yes, that's right.
On my first night,
down by the pantry,
you said that two cars hadn't
come to town on the same day
for a really long time,
and that it was special.
Why?
You've been here the
longest out of anyone.
Do you know what this place is?
Seriously, man, I don't know why
you keep staring at that thing.
I'm sorry. Hold on.
This page, it's...
What?
There's two pages stuck together here.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Okay.
Huh.
Now, we're talking.
Victor!
Holy shit.
You're gonna go to a new home now.
I'm gonna give you to Fatima.
She's gonna take such good care of you.
What are you laughing at?
Hi, Trudy.
How... how do you know my name?
We know all your names.
I'm just saying...
I've been here longer than
him. Deserve a little respect.
I could really help this
place if they just...
What the...?
Is that blood?
Jeez...
What the...?
Ah!
They're in the house! They're inside!
Ellis? Have you seen Ellis?
Ellis!
Follow protocol!
Where's the van?!
Hide!
What's going on?
It's starting.
What? What's starting?
We have to go.
Go where?
Where are we going?
Go where? Hello?
Answer me!
You go first.
I'll follow you down.
Here. Take this.
You ready?
Follow protocol!
Find your buddy! Get
into the van! Come on!
Wait, Donna! What are you doing?
- Where's Ellis and Julie?
- I don't know.
- Hey, Donna!
- I am not running.
Okay. You've gotta get
those people to town.
Save as many as you can.
- Follow protocol.
- Okay, okay.
All right, everyone. Out of the way.
Get in the van!
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Hurry up!
We need to get to town.
- No. We have to go to the trees.
- Are you crazy?
Those things live in there!
- Please!
- They'll kill us!
You have to trust me.
If you want to see your family again,
we have to go to the trees.
Okay.
No!
No.
Baby, no way.
Ellis!
- Hey.
- Hi. Have you seen Julie?
I don't know. I can't...
Okay, we need to go.
We need to run. Come on!
Come on.
No, I can't!
- Come on!
- I can't go! You just go.
I'm not going without you!
Come on, we can do this.
Up, up, up!
Up, up, up! We have to
get back in the house!
We have to get inside!
I have an idea. Come on.
Please! Please, please, please,
please! Please. Please...
Don't be like that.
We were having so much fun.
How'd you know that was gonna work?
I didn't.
With your dad and the RV I just...
I'm sorry.
I love you.
I love you too.
- Where are we going?!
- There's another one here.
- Another what?
- Come on.
You have to get inside.
- The tree? No! No!
- You'll be safe!
- What?
- I promise.
You have to find your
brother. You have to warn him.
You have to tell him it's starting.
I don't know what you're talking about!
He will.
- Go, go, go!
- No, wait!
I'll be right behind you.
If we do this, and I mean "if"...
and she even blinks the wrong way...
You do what you need to do.
But we're goin' out there
and we're gonna find answers.
We're gonna find a way, Boyd.
This, this is why I was
told to get back in the car.
So that you and I
can go out there and find
a way to bring these people home.
You're a fucking madman.
You know that, right?
Bible's full of 'em.
What the fuck?
What happened?!
I... what happened?!
They got in and they...
- Wait! Where's Ellis?
- I don't know!
- Where is Ellis?
- I don't know! Sorry!
Everybody inside. Everybody inside.
- Go! Let's go!
- Everybody inside now!
- Let's go! Let's go! Hustle!
- Keep going! Keep going!
- Let's go! Come on, man!
- Hurry, hurry, hurry! Inside!
- Is that it? Is that it?
- Inside, everybody!
Where are you guys going?
You guys okay over there?
Father...
No!
No, come here!
Close it!
Come on. You got it.
Come on!
Keep him elevated.
Get me something to stop the bleeding!
- Please, no.
- Okay, it's okay.
- Please!
- Let me stop the bleeding!
Please... No.
- You're okay.
- No.
- No...
You're okay. You are okay.
It doesn't end like this.
My path... Please!
Hurry up!
Okay.
I got him.
One...
There we go. There we go.
Open your eyes. Stay with me.
Stay with me.
Pray with me.
- What? Okay.
- Pray with me.
- Okay.
Okay, okay.
Our Father.
Who art in Heaven,
hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come, thy will be done
on earth as it is in heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread...
and forgive us our trespasses
as we forgive those
who trespass against us.
And lead us not into temptation,
but deliver us from evil.
Amen.
Synced & corrected by QueenMaddie
www.addic7ed.com