Previously on From...
Everybody here just talks about
how afraid they are of dying.
Well, I don't think that's the worst
thing that can happen to you here.
When I blacked out in the ruins,
it was almost like I went somewhere.
And then I heard those children.
- They were screaming that word.
- Anghkooey.
The bottle tree was
important to Miranda.
She had visions of these trees.
Somewhere in these numbers is a key
to something that we need to understand.
- There is no baby.
- Yes, there is.
It's just not yours.
Elgin, please.
Fatima is missing.
What we're asking for is a search party.
What if Fatima is out doing
something to help us?
I think she's gonna be okay.
The last place we saw her
was out at the shack,
which is about here.
So, we've got people
covering this whole area
in and around town, which
leaves here, here.
What was she doing?
What?
Out at the shack.
Why was she out there?
Hey.
I think Elgin knows.
I think he knows where Fatima is.
www.subtitulamos.tv
He said she was fine
and that this was all important.
He was so calm about it.
He said I shouldn't be afraid.
Look, I don't know if he just snapped
or if something here is
actually talking to him.
Where is he now?
Colony House.
You two go up there.
And make sure he does not leave.
- Okay. What are you gonna do?
- Just go.
Do you think they found Fatima yet?
I sure hope so.
Victor.
- What are you doing here?
- Your mom fell down.
What?
Thank you, honey.
What happened?
- I'm okay. I'm okay.
- Yeah? Yeah?
Yeah, yeah.
I saw the Boy in White.
Really?
Yeah.
What did he say?
He wasn't very helpful.
Let's go to the diner.
- I don't want to.
- Mom and Dad need to talk. Come on.
- Wanna come?
- No.
Come on. I'm hungry.
The little girl, she led
us to the root cellar.
Victor was there.
He was really upset.
He remembered something about his mother
and the night she left.
When I hugged him...
I felt like Miranda was there.
What do you mean?
I don't know how to explain it,
but I could feel her.
I could feel her in that room.
And then she took me back
to the night it happened,
the night she left her children,
the night she went to the tree.
So you had, like, a vision?
No. No, no, no, no, no.
It was not a vision.
It was more than that.
Somehow, Miranda was there,
and she was trying to tell me something.
We're closed!
You're gonna wanna hear this.
No offense, Jim, but I think
I've heard just about enough.
Look, I'm...
I'm sorry about the way I
came in here yesterday.
I shouldn't have.
I'm scared.
Things are happening in my family
that I don't know how
to protect them from.
But the truth is, I think you might.
I figured you might be here.
I need you to come up to
Colony House with me.
Elgin's been acting strange.
From what Ellis tells me, the kid's been
under a lot of stress,
plus he and Tillie were close.
What happened to her may have just...
Yeah. I don't know. Anyway...
he told Ellis that Fatima and the baby
are gonna be the reason
we all get to go home.
Now, that sound familiar?
- What do you need me to do?
- I need you to talk to him.
Make him understand that if he
really is talking to something here,
its intentions aren't good.
You of all people understand that, okay?
Just remember...
Hey.
What the hell's going on?
Ellis and Kenny are inside,
saying Elgin can't leave.
- Where's Acosta?
- She's still out looking.
I came back to see if
anyone found anything.
How many people you got inside?
I don't know. A few. Most
people are still out searching.
I need you to clear the house.
When she got to the tree...
she was so close.
But one of these things
came from the woods and...
it smiled.
And you watched Miranda die.
You've had visions before, right?
Not like this.
It's always more like I'm seeing
something that shouldn't be there.
Like, that day that I saw
the Civil War soldier,
it's not like I was
back in the Civil War.
This is... this is different.
You said something interesting.
You said that it felt like Miranda
was trying to tell you something.
- I know it sounds crazy.
- No, it doesn't.
Not here, anyway.
Okay.
The first law of thermodynamics
is that energy can neither
be created nor destroyed.
It can only change from
one form to another.
And our thoughts,
our memories...
our souls,
if you believe in that sort of thing,
they're made of energy.
And that energy...
Maybe here, that energy,
I don't know, maybe...
it lingers.
All right, look, you
said it was one of those
creepy kids that led you
to the root cellar, right?
- Yeah, a little girl.
- Okay.
Whatever it was Miranda showed you,
those kids wanted you to see.
Where were you when you
saw the little girl?
Out by Victor's truck.
Elgin.
Mind if we talk to you for a minute?
Yeah.
Okay.
We'll go to my room.
- I'll take that.
- Yeah.
Just in there.
Go on. Have a seat.
Have a seat.
Can you watch the door for me?
I mean, it looks like you,
packed supplies for a couple days.
Where were you going?
I was just...
Yeah.
I'm gonna ask you something,
and I want you to tell me the truth.
Do you know where Fatima is?
- Elgin.
- Answer the question.
She told me not to say anything.
I just...
I know how much you all care about her.
When you told me about your mom...
I can't even imagine what
you're going through.
I wanted to help. I don't
want to hurt anybody.
But you have to understand,
what's happening is a good thing.
Elgin, you said she told
you not to say anything.
Who is she?
I know it sounds crazy,
but I think she's an angel.
- Elgin, there's...
- She's here to help us.
Something is happening
here that's beyond
our ability to understand,
like in the Bible.
People never really understood then.
But they had faith,
even when it was hard,
especially when it's hard.
Fatima's baby is going
to save all of us.
Hey, Elgin, I need you
to listen to me, okay?
- There is no baby.
- That's not true.
Kristi and Marielle did an
ultrasound in the clinic.
And when they pulled up the image,
there was nothing there.
Whatever's growing inside
her is not a child.
The things it's done to her,
the things it's made her do...
You don't understand. She
explained all that to me.
Wait. The angel?
Yes.
Elgin.
The day we met, I...
told you I killed my brother.
Do you know why that happened?
There were voices here
that told me if I killed a little boy,
we would all get to go home.
This place...
it doesn't give.
It takes.
And what it's doing to you...
But do you see how it's different?
No one is dying here.
Fatima is gonna be fine.
You don't fucking know that, okay?
You don't know that!
Once the baby is born,
we all get to go home.
Elgin, even if she's pregnant,
that's still months away.
No. It's grown.
You should see Fatima's belly.
- Okay. Where the fuck is she?
- No, no, no!
- Where the fuck is she?
- I can't!
- Kenny!
- I can't tell you, Ellis!
- Kenny, Kenny!
- I'll fucking kill you!
- Where is she?
- I can't! I can't!
All right! All right! Everybody out!
- Just relax!
- Out! Out! Outside!
Everybody, now! Let's go!
No. He knows where she is, all right?
- I can't just let him sit there!
- I know. I know. Just breathe.
No. I don't need to fucking breathe!
- What I need is to find my wife!
- Listen to me. Listen to me.
We're gonna find out
everything that he knows.
I just need you to calm down.
What he said about the baby,
about how big Fatima's gotten,
do you think it's true?
I don't know, Donna.
He's not gonna tell you!
I know what it's like to have
this place in your head.
If he really believes what he's
saying is gonna save everyone,
he's not gonna tell you where she is.
Where do you keep your tools?
- Boyd.
- Where?
The shed.
They're in the shed.
- Boyd.
- You stay by the door.
He doesn't come out.
No one...
goes back in that room.
Victor.
How are things going with, Jasper?
Did he say anything interesting so far?
It's just a doll. You were right.
Dolls don't talk.
Look. I...
I just wanted to say
I'm sorry I haven't been more help.
All this...
it's been a lot for me.
But that's no excuse.
- From now on...
- I have to show you something.
Okay.
It's gonna make you angry.
It's gonna make you hate me.
What?
But I have to show you.
And then we'll be done.
- Done with what?
- It's this way.
Okay, okay, okay.
You really gonna do this?
I don't got time for you today.
What comes first?
You gonna use the saw or the hammer?
Oh, you know what you should do?
You should go old school.
Get yourself some pliers and
rip his fingernails right off.
Well, if that's what it takes.
You really don't see the irony, do you?
What the fuck are you talking about?
Oh, I don't know. When
Fatima killed Tillie,
you didn't even blink.
I mean, you did everything
you could to protect her.
You took her out to the shed.
You lied to the people
you claim to care about.
Hell, Kenny's in there right now.
He still doesn't know what she did.
What happened wasn't her fault.
Okay, and tell me how that's
any different with Elgin.
I mean, this place got inside his head,
made him think he was
doing something good.
Convinced him he was
actually protecting Fatima.
And now, you're out here getting
ready to go medieval on him.
Bit of a double standard,
don't you think?
It's different.
There's nothing I could do about Tillie.
Oh, bullshit. Tell yourself
anything you want, Boyd.
I mean, you walk around here
like you're some big
knight in shining armor,
Mr. Noble Sheriff.
Push comes to shove, you're no
different than anyone else.
You protect what's yours, and you
fuck anyone who gets in your way.
- You were supposed to be better than this.
- You were supposed to be here!
You were...
You and I were supposed to
figure this out together!
You were the one who went
in the fucking street
and got his throat slit!
So, don't you come in here and judge...
You don't get to judge me.
I'm doing the best I can.
You know there's no coming
back from this, right?
You said that you weren't gonna
let this place break you.
But if you do this,
this place has won.
And if I don't...
my daughter-in-law dies.
Well, that's why they call
it a rock and a hard place,
not a rock and a soft, comfy pillow.
You need to decide
right now who you are,
because that's who you're
gonna be from now on.
Someone open this door!
Please!
What are we doing here?
I thought maybe there was a
reason they came out to you here.
Look. The only thing tying together
all the crazy that we've seen, right?
Me, you, Miranda... The
one point of overlap
in all our Venn diagrams of crazy...
Is the children.
Wait. You've seen them too?
In the cavern.
They were laying on these slabs
of rock, saying that word.
- Anghkooey. Anghkooey.
- Yeah.
Over and over again.
And I looked up.
There was this hole in the ceiling.
And there was this mass of roots,
this tangle forming that fucking symbol.
The roots of the tree.
- What'd you say?
- The Boy in White.
Victor heard him.
He said when the kids
were on the stones,
they poured their hopes into the roots
that made the symbol,
and then those roots became the tree.
Is it the bottle tree?
Yeah, I think so.
Okay. So the... creepy kids
made a magic tree.
And the symbol that has been
plaguing me this whole time...
You could have just fucking told me!
- You didn't have to...
- Jade. Jade.
No, no! I am sick...
I am sick and tired of
getting dicked around!
If you really want our help,
if there is something you
need us to understand,
you're gonna have to do a little better,
because we are not getting it!
You hear me? Message is
not fucking received!
So, we're gonna sit here,
and we're gonna wait.
And when you decide
that you have something more to say
than fucking Anghkooey,
you know where to find us!
You feel better now?
No.
Not really.
You're not giving yourself time to heal.
Fatima's still out there.
I can't just sit here.
I'm gonna get some fresh gauze.
You were really quiet last night,
after they brought Julie in.
I just felt bad. I mean, she's...
Randall?
Hey, what happened to your bandage?
It fell off.
Where's the stuff from the
ambulance, the new stuff?
It's in the cabinets.
No, not the medicine. The equipment.
Where did you put the equipment?
There's a supply closet downstairs.
- Great.
- Randall.
Stop!
I'm trying to make it fucking stop!
Look at me!
Look at me. Hey.
You're gonna be okay.
You're gonna be all right. Come here.
No one comes upstairs.
- Dad, just...
- Nobody comes upstairs.
- You make sure of that, okay?
- Yeah.
What happens next...
that's on me.
Boyd.
Go downstairs now, Kenny.
We should talk to him again.
Look. He's a good kid,
and there's gotta be a way
to make him understand this.
Fatima's out there.
She may be running out of time.
Go downstairs.
Please.
I can't tell you.
I wish I could, but...
but I can't.
I understand.
You need to do what you need to do.
Now I need to do what I need to do.
Motherfucker.
That's how she sends me messages.
I think she wants to talk to you.
Here.
Okay.
Victor, where are we going?
We're here.
We're here?
What is that?
I tried to make it pretty.
The way she would have liked it.
Wait.
This is where I buried Mom.
I thought you'd want to see.
Oh, God.
Is that...
Is that Eloise?
I think so.
All I found were pieces.
She was so small.
There wasn't much left.
It was my fault.
What?
I thought Jasper told
Christopher the secrets.
It wasn't Jasper. It
was the Boy in White.
I was wrong. He told
Christopher about...
about the children and the tree.
But I was the one that told Mom.
I told her that the tree would
bring her to the children.
I was the reason that she
left that night, Dad.
I was the reason that she died.
Victor, you know...
If I'd just not said anything,
she would still be here, and
Eloise would still be here.
No. Victor, you were just a boy. You...
I should have died that night, too.
What?
And you should pretend that I did.
You don't have to be my dad anymore.
No. Wait. Stop.
Goddamn it! I said stop!
You don't ever say that again!
Do you hear me?!
You don't ever...
I'm your dad.
I will never stop being your dad.
Your mother did what she
did because she loved you.
She was trying to protect you.
That's my job now.
Okay?
That's my job.
Listen. If those kids made the tree,
then those messages in the
bottles, the numbers,
they have to matter.
How do we know the
numbers mean anything?
We don't even know who put them there.
Think of all the people
who have been here.
We could be chasing
someone's random delusion.
No! Miranda knew those
bottles were important.
Why else would she have a
replica in her backyard?
She's right.
- There's something there. There has to be
something there. - Of course. There has to be.
All right. Okay. There's
ten numbers, right?
- Two are backwards?
- Yes, the two and the sevens.
Great. So that means there's 12.
And believe me, I have tried
every mathematical,
astronomical, astrological,
Babylonian 12-point numerical
cipher I can imagine.
The Zodiac, months of the year,
fucking eggs in a carton.
Bent over backwards twisting it
into some version of the
Fibonacci sequence.
There's nothing there. Believe me.
Aren't there 12 notes in a scale?
- What'd you say?
- Music.
My mom was a piano teacher.
She used to say that music
is the universal language.
I mean, there are 12
notes in a scale, right?
A through G with the
flats and the sharp.
Tea Cup, you are a fucking genius.
I love you. We need to get to the bar.
- You need to go to your house.
- Why?
Victor's mother had a violin.
He hid it somewhere in your basement.
- Why?
- Because I kept stealing it.
Just meet us at the bar.
Come on, people! Let's go!
How's he doing?
I gave him something that
should help him sleep.
What are we gonna do when he wakes up?
I mean, he tried to...
He had the paddle on his head.
I don't know.
Look. I've...
I've tried to be respectful,
and I've tried to give you space,
but I just really need you
to talk to me right now.
About what?
Randall just tried to
lobotomize himself,
Julie is a mess, and you're
acting like everything's fine.
Hey. Look. I don't know what
the three of you went through,
but I just need you to
tell me if you're okay.
- Kristi.
- No.
Look at me.
Are you okay?
No, I'm not.
And I don't think any
of us are gonna be.
- Okay.
- Please,
can you tell me what was in the picture?
Boyd.
What was in the picture?
- That's what you wanna know, huh?
- Yes. Can you...
Can you just...
Can you tell me what was in the picture?
You wanna know what was
in the picture, do you?
You know what was in
the fucking picture?
I'll tell you what was in the picture.
It was a picture of my house,
the house that I bought with
my wife when I retired,
the one that we were going to
when I ran into that fucking tree.
The only thing missing
was the boat.
Do you see what this means?
She's trying to show you.
We're going home.
All you have to do is wait.
No.
Boyd.
Whatever it is you think you got
to do, you don't have to do it.
I would never, ever hurt Fatima.
She's always been kind to me.
Everything I'm doing is for her.
It's to help us.
If you just give it a
little more time...
We don't have any fucking time!
You took my family.
Do you understand that?
You took someone I love,
and you put her in danger.
I'm sorry about what happened to you.
But we're not gonna wait.
We are not gonna talk.
You're gonna tell me where she is,
- or I am going to hurt you.
- I can't. I can't.
And I'm not gonna stop hurting you
until you tell me what I need to know.
Tell me you understand.
- Tell me!
- I understand.
Good.
Where is she?
Put your hand on the table.
I can't.
No, please.
- No. Boyd.
- We're playing, are we?
Please, Boyd. Just wait.
- Where is she?
- Just...
- It's your last chance.
- I can't. Boyd, I can't.
I can't.
Where is she?!
I don't care!
Hey.
Any news on Fatima?
- What the fuck was that?
- Dani, listen...
Hey! No, no, no!
- Don't let her get up there!
- Dani, you don't understand!
Please, please, Boyd.
Listen, I'm not playing with you!
Where is she?!
Jesus.
What the fuck are you doing?
Turn around and walk out the door!
- Dani, come on.
- Don't fucking touch me!
You do not understand
what is going on here!
Then explain it to me.
- Everyone downstairs.
- What the...
- Dad!
- Downstairs!
Let's go.
How do we know in what order they go in?
Well...
we treat it like any composition.
We try to figure out what is a
chord and what is a melody.
2, 9, 7, 5. 2975.
The 2 is backwards.
So, that would be a G
instead of a B, okay.
Followed by F sharp, D, E. Okay.
So, if it was a melody, it
would be something like...
? G, F sharp, E, D. ?
? G, G, another backwards two, G ?
? G, D, C, C ?
What's wrong?
D, D...
Found it.
- How are you guys coming along?
- No, wait. Wait, wait, wait.
What is that?
I don't know. I don't know. I've
never heard this before. I just...
I looked at the numbers.
I looked at the notes, and I just...
You just what?
I could hear the music.
All right.
Wait.
Hey, stop.
What?! What?!
I'm not so sure this is a good idea.
What are you talking about?
You cracked the code.
Yeah, and the music just
magically popped into your head.
Doesn't that strike you as odd?
Well...
Everything about this place is odd.
And this place is trying
to manipulate us,
to hurt us.
Oh, God. Jim.
How is playing a song gonna hurt us?
Are you forgetting what Boyd said
about the haunted music box
and how it nearly killed everyone
or the jukeboxes in the diner
that just magically
turn on by themselves?
All right. Okay. So, what are you
saying? We just ignore this?
- We forget about it?
- No.
We can't.
Maybe we shouldn't play it here in town,
just to be safe, just to make sure.
I don't know if going out in the
woods is gonna do much good.
I mean, what's the blast
radius on an evil song?
The message was left at the tree.
Maybe we should play it there.
Stop!
No, no.
No, no, no.
No.
It's coming.
What if we forget what she was like?
What?
Tian-Chen.
I don't wanna forget what she was like.
You won't.
Why would you think that?
Because I'm starting to
forget what Thomas was like.
I have to tell you something.
When we went to those ruins,
when I walked inside, I...
I didn't just have a dream.
I think I went somewhere.
What do you mean?
I don't know how, but I...
When we went to the ruins,
suddenly I was in a chamber.
And I saw me and Randall and
Marielle chained to the wall.
What were you doing?
We were screaming.
I think that's where we were
when we couldn't wake up.
But then I left the chamber,
and I went into the tunnels.
I heard Mom's voice.
And she was talking to Victor.
Remember how she said that Victor
was the one who helped her find
her way out of the tunnels
that night when the house fell down?
I think that's what I heard,
but I think I was actually there,
like...
like I somehow went back to that night.
You're a Storywalker.
What?
Someone who can visit
chapters of the story
that already happened.
What...
So, I go back to those ruins,
do you think I could do it again?
Maybe.
- Why?
- Well, if...
this is real,
that means I can change things.
I can save Tian-Chen.
Maybe I could even save Thomas.
It doesn't work like that.
- But you just said...
- You can visit the chapters.
But you can't change them.
Why?
No one can change a story
once it's been told.
It is not what it looks like.
No? Because it looked like
you were torturing that kid.
- You're really okay with this?
- He knows where Fatima is.
Look. I get that you wanna find her.
Okay? I do.
But there is a right and
a wrong way to do this.
Tell me the right way.
You got all the answers! Tell
me the right way to do this!
I don't know, but maybe something that
doesn't involve torturing a scared kid.
Sara.
Hi, Elgin.
I'd tell you if I could, but... I can't.
It's okay.
I understand.
That first day,
when I saw you in the church,
my heart broke for you.
I thought, "He seems so sweet,
so kind."
I was like that once.
I think...
maybe we're exactly what
this place looks for.
No.
People who just want to help.
Sara, can you please tell Boyd to stop?
He'll listen to you.
If we just wait a little longer...
Then Fatima could die.
- No. She's not... Sara, no.
- Yes. Yes.
I know you don't believe that.
I know that you think that
you're saving everyone.
Sara, please.
Boyd doesn't understand
how far he needs to go
to make you tell him.
Don't...
He's a good man.
And this place,
it's taken so much from him.
I won't let it take his soul.
Sara.
I've already given it mine.
This is not Camden! I'm not
debating this with you!
It's happening! You got a problem?
Take it up with me after Fatima is safe!
Is this what you mean by trust?
Okay. How's it gonna play when I go
and tell everyone what you're doing?
Are you...
Shit.
Go!
Sara?
Hey. Sara.
Sara, what...
She's in the root cellar.
If anyone's having second thoughts,
speak now or forever hold your peace.
Go ahead.
Fatima!
Hey. I'm here. I'm here.
She took it.
What?
The thing, she took it down there.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay now.
We're gonna get you out of here.
Dad?
You and Kenny get her
back to Colony House.
What?
- I need to see it.
- Boyd, we...
Look. Whatever this is,
I'm not gonna be blindsided
by this place again.
- No. Dad, what are you... You can't...
- Look. Go.
Take care of your wife.
I'll be right behind you, okay?
They're here.
What?
Where?
Do you see them?
Come on. Keep playing. Keep playing.
You're okay.
No. Ellis, I saw them.
I saw what they did.
What?
Those things that come out at night,
I saw what they are.
They sacrificed their... their children,
because It promised them that
they would live forever.
Anghkooey.
Remember.
- What's that?
- Anghkooey.
It means "remember."
- We tried to save them...
- No.
- because one of them...
- No, no, no, no.
Oh, God.
No, no, no. I can't. I can't. I can't.
What just happened?
We used to sing them lullabies.
Tabitha.
- No, I can't.
- Hey. Hey.
- No, no, no, no, no. I can't.
- Tab...
You can't?
Please, talk to me.
I know why.
I know why I see those children.
- Okay.
- Why Jade can see them.
It's why there's more than one bracelet.
I kept making them.
Somewhere deep down, I remember.
I don't know what the
fuck you're saying!
I don't understand.
It's because we've been here before,
me and Jade.
The reason I felt what Miranda felt
is because I was Miranda.
And Jade...
Jade was Christopher.
We've come back over and over again
because we failed the first time.
- The first time?
- Yes.
Jade and I were here at the beginning.
We tried to save those
children and set them free...
because one of them was ours.
She was our daughter.
No.
No, that's...
It's true. It's true. I feel it.
And I need some time, honey.
Can you give me some time?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Sometimes I remember what it was like
when it wasn't like this.
What it was like before.
Dad! Can you hear me?!
- Julie?!
- Dad!
I'm over here!
Over here!
Dad! Dad, you have to run! You
need to get to town right now!
- What's happened to you?
- You need to listen to me!
It's not safe! I don't... I
think this is when it happens!
- Okay. Slow down. We're okay.
- No, no. Listen to me.
I need to change the story. Dad, please!
That was a hell of a song.
That Jade sure can play.
Get outta here.
- No, you don't understand.
- Run. Run. Run.
This didn't have to happen, you know.
Back up.
Knowledge comes with a cost.
- I said back the fuck up!
- Dad, please!
Dad, please!
I did try to warn you.
Get off him!
Your wife shouldn't have
dug that hole, Jim.
No!
www.subtitulamos.tv