Previously on From.
Fuck! Just get this
fucking thing off of me.
Pull! Pull!
- Shit. Are you good?
- My ankle.
- It's dislocated.
- All right.
- Let's get her back to camp.
- Okay.
I wanna catch one of those things.
We need to learn about them.
We catch one. We make it talk.
Maybe we switch tonight.
- I'll take the bus.
- Why?
Because I wanna watch our friends when
they come out of the woods tonight.
We need to build a fort.
Then I'm gonna tell a story.
Are those the crops?
Yeah. We figured we'd
try composting them.
Whatever's going on,
I promise it'll pass.
Is my baby okay?
Let's see what the cards have to say.
Miranda used to call it the bottle tree.
The original's in a
park a few towns over.
Miranda made that for me.
This can't be real.
I found this in the diner.
Pull over right now!
- No!
- No, no!
We're going!
Where am I?
There's a tree in the
middle of the road.
Unit 4-5. Unit 4-5.
Hospital, do you copy?
Do you copy?
Unit 4-5. Unit 4-5. Mechanical en route.
Copy. Copy.
Just getting static.
Where is everyone?
Should be at least a little
traffic this time of day.
Yeah, well, we're not
gonna move it, so...
My God.
Unit 4-5. Do you copy?
- Oh, my God.
- We're 30, 35 out.
We got a tree blocking the road.
Unit 4-5. Do you copy?
Miss, I need you to get
back in the vehicle.
No.
Unit 4-5. Unit 4-5. Do...
Just take a detour! Go around it!
Ma'am, let's get back inside.
- It's not gonna work.
- It's okay.
- We'll take another way. It's okay.
It's okay.
- It's all right.
- It's not gonna work.
- It'll be okay. We'll get you back inside.
- You have to listen to me!
Come on.
Hello?
Ethan? It's Thomas.
Mommy's in trouble.
She's in an ambulance.
What ambulance?
You'll see. She's on her way,
but you have to help her.
You can't be afraid.
Who is this?
I told you. It's Thomas.
Who is this really?
Who is this?
Who are you talking to?
He says he's Thomas.
Hi, Jim.
You leave my children alone.
But they're not your children anymore.
Dad?
What did he say?
Ethan, I need you to talk to me.
That Mom was alive.
She's on an ambulance.
She needs our help.
www.subtitulamos.tv
What are you waiting for? Pick it up.
You pick it up. I'm not
touching that thing.
It's dead. What are you worried about?
That bird just went kamikaze
through a plate-glass
window to get in here.
Whatever bad juju that thing has,
I don't want any part of it.
And by the way,
I don't mean to ask the
obvious question here,
but do you think it's really smart to
do tarot readings in a place like this?
- I'm sorry. I didn't mean to...
- Hey, that's enough.
We got plenty to worry about without
people sniping at each other.
Hey, you all right?
I'm good.
You sure?
I had no idea things were
so exciting up here.
Open.
You're good.
Look, this really is not necessary.
Don't be silly.
I make it a point to
examine all my patients
after they've had encounters
with psychotic birds.
Besides, it's helping take my mind off
of Kristi being out at that lake.
No. They'll be fine.
They've got shelter.
They've got talismans.
- It's all you need.
- I know.
But...
if it was Ellis, I would
be feeling the same way.
Drink.
It's nice to just be
taking care of a pregnant
Mama bear again.
You look much better.
Your color's improved.
You've been eating a little more?
Yeah.
Finally found something
I could keep down.
Great. Get that baby nice and strong.
We used to play in here.
Not at night.
At nighttime, everyone had to hide.
There were no talismans then.
But during the daytime,
my sister and I would
play inside the houses.
We pretended that we were home again.
She always liked this one the
best, and I never knew why.
You came here with your sister?
My mother, too, but they died.
Just like Nathan,
except I didn't murder them.
Is this enough?
Yeah, that's good.
I don't understand what we're doing.
I told you, I have to remember.
Remember what?
When I was a boy, my mother
tried to save everyone, but she died.
And then everyone died, and
I can't remember how...
or why.
And I think I need to remember soon.
Why?
Too many things are changing.
It's never snowed here before.
We have to go in the basement.
Up here is for daytime stories.
The basement's for secrets.
Hello? Unit 4-5.
How are we still in the goddamn woods?
We were right outside the city
when we stopped at that tree.
What does the GPS say?
Same thing it said ten minutes ago...
data unavailable.
We gotta be driving in circles.
The woods aren't this deep.
- Okay, fine. I'll turn around.
- No, no, no! Please don't turn around!
Just keep going forward.
- Lady, calm down.
- If you turn around,
you'll be driving away from town!
What town? We're looking
for the highway.
I know, I know, but...
You have to listen to me. It's...
It's not safe to stop out
here once it gets dark,
but there's a town up ahead,
and people there can help us.
You just need to keep
going forward, please.
So, you're gonna watch these things,
get a sense of how they
move and what they do,
and that's gonna what?
Give you some grand insight into
how you're gonna catch one?
Yeah.
Something like that.
Yeah. Okay.
I'm sure nothing terrible
is gonna come of that.
Why are you here?
What do you mean?
I said we could switch.
You could be fast asleep by
now in the sheriff's station.
So, why are you here?
That's none of your business.
What the fuck do you care, anyway?
'Cause if I gotta stand here
all night and listen to you,
I'd at least like to know why that is.
Look, if you're gonna do something
that has even the slightest chance
of getting us the hell out of here,
no matter how stupid or ill-advised
that thing might be...
then I wanna help.
So, now, all of a sudden,
you're a team player.
If you'd seen the things I've seen,
then you might be, too.
What are you talking about,
seen the things you've seen?
What do you think I'm
talking about, Boyd?
Me, Julie, Marielle,
wherever we were.
Everybody here just talks about
how afraid they are of dying.
I don't think that's the worst thing
that can happen to you here.
I want out.
You should get some sleep.
Tomorrow's gonna be a long day.
Sorry. Did I wake you up?
No. The, throbbing pain in my ankle did.
Is there anything I can do
to help make it better?
No, not until, some of
the swelling goes down.
What are you writing?
It's just... something for my mom.
In Chinese culture,
we write letters to the
dead on high holidays.
It's not really a
holiday, I guess, but...
I think she'd really like that.
Yep.
I meant what I said earlier.
You're not alone here.
Things are different now. That's all.
Yeah.
It just feels like...
all of a sudden...
everything that I thought I
was fighting for is gone.
And everything that I thought
I was going home to.
And the two people that I
would talk to about that
are you and Mom.
You can still talk to me.
Could you maybe talk in the morning?
Sorry.
Fuck it.
I'm awake.
Hey.
You guys wanna hear something crazy?
The night everyone died,
I was in the root cellar.
My mother told Eloise
and I to hide there.
Eloise didn't listen.
But I did.
I stayed until morning.
And when I came out,
there were bodies everywhere.
That was the day that I
met the boy in white.
You know the boy in white?
He's my friend.
He was my only friend all
those years that I was alone.
Couldn't bury them all.
They were just lying there
in the street, and...
I couldn't bury them.
So the boy in white
told me to...
gather things that
were precious to them.
To bury those instead.
This stuff...
that'll help you remember
why it happened?
I think so.
Why are we in here?
Because it's a fort.
Why do you need me?
Because I don't want to do this alone.
I may have to remember
some scary things.
And you're the scariest person here,
so it won't scare you.
You always this fidgety?
Something's wrong.
Those things should be all
over the place by now.
Really?
These things give "creature of
habit" a whole new goddamn meaning.
The one in the nurse's uniform?
I'm her first stop every night,
every single night.
She just stands by the
glass, and she hums.
For about ten minutes, she just stands,
taps on the glass with
her fucking smile.
And there's another one, right? Likes
to sit over there by the swing.
- Okay.
- Just letting its legs dangle.
There's another couple like to sit
over there by the pool, just...
You really watch these things closely.
Yeah, well, there's no TV.
Plus, you guys get to draw the
shades at night. I got...
Look. The point is, they
got patterns, routines,
all of which should be
happening right now.
Right now.
- Ma'am, you're not making any sense.
- I know this road.
There's a town up ahead. The
people there can help us
- find the highway again. I promise you.
- Okay.
We just need to keep going that way.
We're here! The barn is here!
- Stop! Stop here!
- Lady, we're fine, okay?
We're not gonna stop in
the middle of nowhere.
Fuck.
Oh, shit. What the...
What the fuck?
It's an ambulance, just like he said!
Mom!
Oh, no, no.
- Get in here!
- I got him.
- No! No!
- Got him.
- Let's get back inside.
- No! Mom!
You need to stop. Please stop.
Lady. I'm not gonna
tell you again, okay?
Shit.
- What's wrong?
- We got a body in the road.
What if Mom's really out there?
What's he talking about?
The voice on the phone said
she'd be on an ambulance.
There's somebody lying in
the middle of the road.
No.
It's not a fucking person!
- That is not a fucking person!
- Okay!
We're just gonna calm down, okay?
- No, no, no!
- Go ahead. I got this.
You are not fucking listening to me.
Where are you going? Don't go.
- Please don't fucking go!
- Move!
- If you fucking leave you're gonna
fucking die! - Ma'am! Ma'am.
Okay. You need to calm down!
You need to fucking calm down!
They're gonna die!
They're gonna fucking die!
- Jesus.
- Oh, my God.
Ma'am, can you hear me?
- Okay.
- Here. Help me roll her over. Come on.
Watch her head.
I'm not getting a pulse.
Hey, guys!
Lady's really freaking out back here.
What the...
Oh, my God!
Back up!
- Okay.
- Those were gunshots!
Which means those things
are already out there.
Oh, my God.
- Henry?
- What?
It's okay.
- We're okay.
If there's even a chance
my wife is out there...
You do what you want.
Okay. Listen. You gotta stay inside.
Whoever's on that ambulance,
you'll be putting them in danger if
we have to worry about you, okay?
I need you to tell me you understand.
- I understand.
- Julie?
Yeah.
We are in real danger right now.
There are things in this
town that will hurt us
if we don't get inside
one of the houses.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God!
Oh, mother of God!
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! Jim! Jim!
Tabitha.
Help me! Help me! Please help me, baby!
Please help us!
- Are there keys?
- I don't know! I don't know where they are!
Everybody, out of the ambulance, now!
- Jesus.
- What the fuck?
Handcuffs.
- What?
- You have handcuffs. Hand me the keys.
I don't have them.
- No...
- There's a toolkit on the bus.
- I got it. Got it!
- No! Wait, wait!
All right! Stay, stay, stay!
Runner on the hill!
I think it's a cop.
What the fuck?
- What was that?
- Nicky's been shot!
Excuse me.
What happened?
- Did she hit her head?
- I don't know.
- Get that window boarded up.
- Here, get her onto the couch.
Let her have some air.
- Come on.
- All right. All right.
It's Nicky?
Hey, Nicky. I'm Marielle.
I'm gonna help you, okay?
Easy, easy.
Help me roll her onto her side.
Okay. All right.
Okay. No exit wound. We need
to get this bullet out.
Hey, open up!
I'm a police officer!
- Hey, move.
- What are you doing? - Please!
- She's a cop. We can't just leave
her out there. - Open the door!
- We should wait for Kristi.
- Kristi's not back until tomorrow.
We need to do this now. Hey, I'm
gonna need a lot of things.
Tweezers, pliers, alcohol, and towels.
Okay. Yeah, yeah.
I know.
Okay.
- Yes.
- Oh, my God.
Okay.
Oh, God.
- Those things were coming from
everywhere. I didn't mean to... - You not!
No. Listen. You gotta believe me.
Please, you gotta believe me.
- It must have been a misfire!
- I said back the fuck up!
Oh, God. This isn't real.
This isn't real. This can't be
happening. This isn't real.
- Is there anyone with you?
- What?
- Is there anyone else out there?
- Is she gonna be okay?
How did you get here?
We were in an ambulance.
There was this tree.
Where are the fucking keys.
Get the fuck back.
I said get the fuck back!
Oh, sweetie, it doesn't work that way.
Hey, get back to the bus!
Hey, Jim!
Hey. Tools.
Boyd, we got to go.
Get something! Get something!
I can't find the fucking keys!
- Where the...
- Are you looking for these?
Motherfucker!
Take them.
We get to keep Randall, though.
Get off me!
You can't save them all.
Boyd, let's go! We
gotta get out of here!
Fuck you! Fuck you!
Motherfuckers.
Fuck you!
Boyd? Boyd, don't you leave
me, you piece of shit!
Apply pressure right here.
Okay. All right. Good.
- Good. Okay. Good.
- Yeah?
- Are you sure you've got this?
- Yeah. Yeah. I got it.
Sit here. Hold her legs down.
- Okay. Okay. I got it.
- Keep her still.
- Come on.
- Okay? - Yeah.
Little sting. I know. I know. I know.
Shit. Okay. Let me see.
Okay. Let me see.
Bite down. Bite down.
- Hold her very still.
- Come on, Nicky.
Here we go.
All right. Here we go. I know. I know.
- You got this.
- All right.
It's okay. It's okay.
Okay. I think I got it.
Okay.
Okay. We got it.
Yeah.
Good job.
There's a woman in the ambulance.
There were two paramedics outside,
and I don't know where she is, but
this is probably 20 minutes...
It's okay.
- Oh, my God! Yes, yes, yes!
- That's it. That's it. Okay.
- Thank you.
- All right. Can you get up?
- Yes.
- Yeah?
Henry, let's go. Let's go, Henry.
- And you? Can you walk?
- I think so.
Come on. Come on. I got you. I got you.
You okay?
- I got him!
- Oh, my God! Hurry!
I got him. I got him. I got him.
I got him. Come here. Come here.
I got you. I got you.
Let's go.
There you go. Come on.
There you go.
There you go. Close that door.
You okay?
Look.
Bad idea.
Hey, what happened?
It was a long night.
For everyone, it seems.
I fucking told you.
Donna, can we...
You can. I'll put you
in a room upstairs.
Are you okay?
Yes.
- Yeah.
- Come on.
That poor girl.
Nicky's gonna be all right.
No. I'm not talking about Nicky.
I'm talking about Fatima.
That horrible bird.
What if it was a sign?
What's wrong?
Am I awake?
Where are you going?
Help me.
- Please.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Can you see anything?
No.
What if they don't come back?
Don't think like that.
They'll come back.
Julie,
what happened to you?
What do you mean?
Ever since you fell asleep
and your eyes got all white,
you've been different.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yeah.
Yeah. I'm fine.
I don't believe you.
You know I'm not a baby anymore.
You can tell me things.
You wanna know the truth?
I'm really scared.
I saw things that I don't
really understand.
There's things that I
can't even remember.
All I remember is being more scared
than I've ever been in my entire life.
And that's the truth.
I haven't told anybody but you.
I'm trying really hard to be okay.
Can I help?
Hey, I'm the big sister here.
I'm the one who takes care of you.
If they don't come back,
it'll just be us.
We have to start taking care
of each other from now on.
They'll come back.
So, the rod was through his eye?
Only when he was on the tree. When he...
walked up to me with a skull
full of blood, it was just a...
a bloody, empty socket.
- Jesus.
- Yeah.
So, that's what my
life's been like lately.
How long has this been going on for?
The hallucinating?
Pretty much since I got here.
Do you remember that day I took
you down to the root cellar,
told you I saw that symbol up on the
ceiling? You thought I was crazy?
Tian-Chen
saw me in the diner.
I was drawing the symbol over
and over again, losing my mind,
and first, she made me tea.
And then she took me back into
the storage room, and she...
she pulled out this.
Still have no idea how
she knew it was there.
My mom knew every inch
of that storage room.
You know, I thought I was smart enough
to figure this place out, and...
I should have...
Fuck.
She really liked you, you know?
My mom.
I think she tolerated
me more than anything.
No, no, no. I mean, she really...
She only frowned at
people that she liked.
I mean, the people that
she didn't, she just...
ignored.
When you finish that letter,
tell her we all say hi.
Jesus.
Are you sure those things you
saw today were hallucinations?
This belonged to Mr. Gerber.
He always smelled like onions.
They grow wild in the woods,
so he would pick them and eat them raw.
This was from Delores.
She always cried lots.
What's wrong?
Nothing for Christopher.
Who was Christopher?
He was our friend.
He was nice, but then he
started seeing the symbol,
and then he started getting scary.
What?
No. This was a mistake. I don't
want to do this anymore.
- Victor.
- No! I said no!
- Victor!
- I said no!
- No, no, no, no!
- Victor!
- No, no!
- Victor! Victor!
- It's okay.
- No.
You don't have to be afraid.
I'm the scariest person
in town, remember?
I know what's missing.
Hello, Victor!
His name was Jasper.
I...
I left him.
I just...
I just fucking left.
Oh, my God, Boyd.
You know, I couldn't... I...
I tried to save everybody.
What the fuck was Tabitha doing in
the back of that goddamn ambulance?
How did she...
Are you sure he's
really Victor's father?
Jim, I stood in the house
that Victor grew up in.
Jesus.
His mother, Miranda,
she saw this place before
she even got here.
She had these paintings and...
I think that was the reason
why I was sent there.
The little boy in the tower
I think he wanted me to
see something, find something.
And I tried.
I just...
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
You have nothing to be sorry about.
You are back, and you are safe.
And that is all that matters.
But...
But what if that was our
only chance to go home?
- Is she all right?
- Oh, shit.
Nicky?
- What's wrong with her?
- No.
Oh, my God. What is...
- What...
- She's bleeding internally.
The bullet must have done
more damage than I...
Nicky, Nicky, Nicky, stay with me, okay?
You're okay.
- Nicky? Shit.
- Come on, Nicky.
Come on.
Nicky, stay with me! Nicky?
- No.
- Oh, no.
Come on.
Shit. Come on.
- Nicky?
- Jesus.
Oh, no.
You see what you've done?
It was an accident.
What's wrong with you, Officer?
Something scares you, you just
start shooting? Is that right?
- I'm sorry.
- You're sorry? You're sorry?
Come tell Nicky you're sorry!
- Come on now.
- Get the fuck off me!
- Listen!
- You come with me right fucking now!
God!
Shut the door.
Look. I'm not really in the
mood for a lecture right now,
so if all we're gonna do...
Donna?
Why is this happening?
Why is it just one thing
after another after another?
Why can't they stop?
Why can't they leave us alone?
I don't know. I don't know.
Oh, Boyd, I am so fucking scared.
I'm so fucking scared.
All right.
Jasper belonged to Christopher.
He used to be so much fun.
Christopher would make us all laugh.
And people didn't laugh much back then,
so it was very nice that we could.
But then Christopher
started seeing the symbol,
and he changed.
He didn't make us laugh anymore.
I remember...
Christopher started spending
more and more time alone.
And one day...
Jasper's the one who can
tell us why it happened.
Thanks.
I was so mean to her the other day.
Nah.
Every single person in this
house has been on edge lately.
Yeah, but I just think I'm gonna
sit with her for a little bit.
- Yeah. Do you want me to stay?
- No. I think I want to do this alone.
Okay.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
Okay.
Better fuckin' days.
Hear, hear.
www.subtitulamos.tv